Lol	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

Jim	1	B-PER	email

With	0	O	answers
going	0	O	answers
outside	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
put	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
leash	0	O	answers
on	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
just	0	O	answers
take	0	O	answers
him	0	O	answers
for	0	O	answers
a	0	O	answers
walk	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

I	0	O	answers
have	0	O	answers
many	0	O	answers
friends	0	O	answers
that	0	O	answers
have	0	O	answers
laptops	0	O	answers
bought	0	O	answers
in	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
UK	1	B-LOC	answers
that	0	O	answers
use	0	O	answers
them	0	O	answers
here	0	O	answers

10/23/2000	0	O	email
12:12	0	O	email
PM	0	O	email

It	0	O	newsgroup
is	0	O	newsgroup
short	0	O	newsgroup
for	0	O	newsgroup
San	1	B-LOC	newsgroup
Francisco	1	I-LOC	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

What	0	O	weblogs
do	0	O	weblogs
the	0	O	weblogs
new	0	O	weblogs
al	1	B-ORG	weblogs
-	1	I-ORG	weblogs
Qaeda	1	I-ORG	weblogs
videotape	0	O	weblogs
and	0	O	weblogs
audio	0	O	weblogs
speeches	0	O	weblogs
of	0	O	weblogs
Bin	1	B-PER	weblogs
Laden	1	I-PER	weblogs
and	0	O	weblogs
Ayman	1	B-PER	weblogs
al	1	I-PER	weblogs
-	1	I-PER	weblogs
Zawahiri	1	I-PER	weblogs
tell	0	O	weblogs
us	0	O	weblogs
about	0	O	weblogs
the	0	O	weblogs
hopes	0	O	weblogs
of	0	O	weblogs
the	0	O	weblogs
remaining	0	O	weblogs
top	0	O	weblogs
leadership	0	O	weblogs
of	0	O	weblogs
the	0	O	weblogs
organization	0	O	weblogs
?	0	O	weblogs

11/29/2000	0	O	email
09:52	0	O	email
AM	0	O	email

We	0	O	answers
had	0	O	answers
a	0	O	answers
great	0	O	answers
time	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
visited	0	O	answers
a	0	O	answers
location	0	O	answers
where	0	O	answers
they	0	O	answers
made	0	O	answers
coconut	0	O	answers
candies	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
visited	0	O	answers
a	0	O	answers
local	0	O	answers
restaurant	0	O	answers
which	0	O	answers
was	0	O	answers
attached	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
a	0	O	answers
fish	0	O	answers
farm	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
rode	0	O	answers
in	0	O	answers
modified	0	O	answers
quad	0	O	answers
bikes	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
had	0	O	answers
some	0	O	answers
tropical	0	O	answers
food	0	O	answers
at	0	O	answers
what	0	O	answers
appeared	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
be	0	O	answers
a	0	O	answers
local	0	O	answers
hangout	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

He	0	O	answers
was	0	O	answers
so	0	O	answers
eager	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
go	0	O	answers
in	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
nest	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
feed	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
baby	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
she	0	O	answers
always	0	O	answers
would	0	O	answers
go	0	O	answers
right	0	O	answers
away	0	O	answers
in	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
nest	0	O	answers
after	0	O	answers
him	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
give	0	O	answers
him	0	O	answers
a	0	O	answers
fight	0	O	answers
right	0	O	answers
there	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
were	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
baby	0	O	answers
was	0	O	answers
too	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

I	0	O	email
will	0	O	email
deliver	0	O	email
it	0	O	email
to	0	O	email
you	0	O	email
for	0	O	email
your	0	O	email
approval	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

It	0	O	reviews
's	0	O	reviews
a	0	O	reviews
pretty	0	O	reviews
typical	0	O	reviews
primary	0	O	reviews
care	0	O	reviews
office	0	O	reviews
but	0	O	reviews
for	0	O	reviews
the	0	O	reviews
area	0	O	reviews
it	0	O	reviews
's	0	O	reviews
very	0	O	reviews
good	0	O	reviews
.	0	O	reviews

Can	0	O	email
you	0	O	email
get	0	O	email
it	0	O	email
signed	0	O	email
ASAP	0	O	email
and	0	O	email
back	0	O	email
to	0	O	email
me	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

100	0	O	answers
%	0	O	answers
SCAM	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

Please	0	O	email
respond	0	O	email
to	0	O	email
kaplan	1	B-PER	email

4	0	O	email
-	0	O	email
easy	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

Originally	0	O	newsgroup
christened	0	O	newsgroup
Micro	1	B-ORG	newsgroup
-	1	I-ORG	newsgroup
Soft	1	I-ORG	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
'	0	O	newsgroup
-	0	O	newsgroup
'	0	O	newsgroup
was	0	O	newsgroup
removed	0	O	newsgroup
later	0	O	newsgroup
on	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

A	0	O	weblogs
suit	0	O	weblogs
against	0	O	weblogs
the	0	O	weblogs
New	1	B-ORG	weblogs
York	1	I-ORG	weblogs
Times	1	I-ORG	weblogs
and	0	O	weblogs
columnist	0	O	weblogs
Nicholas	1	B-PER	weblogs
Kristof	1	I-PER	weblogs
was	0	O	weblogs
dismissed	0	O	weblogs
in	0	O	weblogs
late	0	O	weblogs
November	0	O	weblogs
2004	0	O	weblogs
.	0	O	weblogs

Confirmation	0	O	email
Desk	0	O	email
:	0	O	email
you	0	O	email
can	0	O	email
stop	0	O	email
adding	0	O	email
the	0	O	email
rep	0	O	email
to	0	O	email
the	0	O	email
confirms	0	O	email
now	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

Merrist	1	B-ORG	answers
Wood	1	I-ORG	answers
in	0	O	answers
Woking	1	B-LOC	answers
in	0	O	answers
Surrey	1	B-LOC	answers
.	0	O	answers

To	0	O	weblogs
not	0	O	weblogs
buying	0	O	weblogs
the	0	O	weblogs
BS	0	O	weblogs

SPLOID.com	1	B-MISC	weblogs
cited	0	O	weblogs
you	0	O	weblogs
on	0	O	weblogs
the	0	O	weblogs
topic	0	O	weblogs
of	0	O	weblogs
that	0	O	weblogs
priest	0	O	weblogs
conviction	0	O	weblogs
:	0	O	weblogs
http://www.sploid.com/news/2006/05/evil_priest_gui.php	1	B-MISC	weblogs

Google	1	B-ORG	newsgroup
Search	0	O	newsgroup
Terms	0	O	newsgroup
:	0	O	newsgroup

The	0	O	newsgroup
Sunburn	1	B-MISC	newsgroup
is	0	O	newsgroup
also	0	O	newsgroup
superior	0	O	newsgroup
to	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
Exocet	1	B-MISC	newsgroup
missile	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

Maybe	0	O	email
we	0	O	email
can	0	O	email
go	0	O	email
drinking	0	O	email
too	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

Below	0	O	newsgroup
are	0	O	newsgroup
some	0	O	newsgroup
emails	0	O	newsgroup
to	0	O	newsgroup
friends	0	O	newsgroup
explaining	0	O	newsgroup
a	0	O	newsgroup
little	0	O	newsgroup
more	0	O	newsgroup
about	0	O	newsgroup
this	0	O	newsgroup
effort	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

We	0	O	email
need	0	O	email
responses	0	O	email
or	0	O	email
direction	0	O	email
by	0	O	email
no	0	O	email
later	0	O	email
than	0	O	email
COB	0	O	email
on	0	O	email
Monday	0	O	email
,	0	O	email
October	0	O	email
30	0	O	email
,	0	O	email
2000	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

Have	0	O	email
a	0	O	email
great	0	O	email
day	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

Why	0	O	answers
is	0	O	answers
it	0	O	answers
stil	0	O	answers
doing	0	O	answers
this	0	O	answers
even	0	O	answers
though	0	O	answers
I	0	O	answers
do	0	O	answers
n't	0	O	answers
have	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
other	0	O	answers
phone	0	O	answers
connected	0	O	answers
?	0	O	answers

After	0	O	reviews
recently	0	O	reviews
relocating	0	O	reviews
to	0	O	reviews
South	1	B-LOC	reviews
Bend	1	I-LOC	reviews
,	0	O	reviews
we	0	O	reviews
were	0	O	reviews
looking	0	O	reviews
for	0	O	reviews
a	0	O	reviews
delicious	0	O	reviews
,	0	O	reviews
fun	0	O	reviews
,	0	O	reviews
yet	0	O	reviews
elegant	0	O	reviews
establishment	0	O	reviews
for	0	O	reviews
New	0	O	reviews
Year	0	O	reviews
s	0	O	reviews
Eve	0	O	reviews
dinner	0	O	reviews
.	0	O	reviews

Notice	0	O	email
Regarding	0	O	email
Entry	0	O	email
of	0	O	email
Orders	0	O	email
and	0	O	email
Instructions	0	O	email
:	0	O	email
Please	0	O	email
do	0	O	email
not	0	O	email
transmit	0	O	email
orders	0	O	email
and	0	O	email
/	0	O	email
or	0	O	email
instructions	0	O	email
regarding	0	O	email
your	0	O	email
PaineWebber	1	B-ORG	email
account	0	O	email
(	0	O	email
s	0	O	email
)	0	O	email
by	0	O	email
e-mail	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

Although	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
I	0	O	answers
do	0	O	answers
n't	0	O	answers
think	0	O	answers
that	0	O	answers
scary	0	O	answers
movies	0	O	answers
will	0	O	answers
affect	0	O	answers
pets	0	O	answers
for	0	O	answers
a	0	O	answers
long	0	O	answers
time	0	O	answers
;	0	O	answers
I	0	O	answers
am	0	O	answers
sure	0	O	answers
they	0	O	answers
'll	0	O	answers
forget	0	O	answers
sometime	0	O	answers
--	0	O	answers
or	0	O	answers
am	0	O	answers
I	0	O	answers
wrong	0	O	answers
?	0	O	answers

Spring	0	O	answers
(	0	O	answers
February	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
April	0	O	answers
)	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
Autumn	0	O	answers
(	0	O	answers
August	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
October	0	O	answers
)	0	O	answers
make	0	O	answers
good	0	O	answers
alternatives	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
although	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
country	0	O	answers
’s	0	O	answers
ever	0	O	answers
-	0	O	answers
growing	0	O	answers
popularity	0	O	answers
as	0	O	answers
a	0	O	answers
tourist	0	O	answers
destination	0	O	answers
can	0	O	answers
often	0	O	answers
blur	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
lines	0	O	answers
between	0	O	answers
mid	0	O	answers
-	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
high	0	O	answers
-	0	O	answers
season	0	O	answers
tourism	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

My	0	O	reviews
favorite	0	O	reviews
florist	0	O	reviews
!	0	O	reviews

and	0	O	answers
how	0	O	answers
big	0	O	answers
are	0	O	answers
they	0	O	answers
?	0	O	answers

All	0	O	email
,	0	O	email

Hi	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
i	0	O	answers
bought	0	O	answers
my	0	O	answers
Syrian	1	B-LOCderiv	answers
Hamster	0	O	answers
(	0	O	answers
Fernando	1	B-PER	answers
)	0	O	answers
just	0	O	answers
yesterday	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
as	0	O	answers
i	0	O	answers
was	0	O	answers
told	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
leave	0	O	answers

I	0	O	email
will	0	O	email
be	0	O	email
in	0	O	email
Sao	1	B-LOC	email
Paulo	1	I-LOC	email
on	0	O	email
Monday	0	O	email
,	0	O	email
September	0	O	email
20	0	O	email
,	0	O	email
1999	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

"	0	O	weblogs
Another	0	O	weblogs
generation	0	O	weblogs
of	0	O	weblogs
heavy	0	O	weblogs
metal	0	O	weblogs
has	0	O	weblogs
taken	0	O	weblogs
over	0	O	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
and	0	O	weblogs
--	0	O	weblogs
sorry	0	O	weblogs
--	0	O	weblogs
it	0	O	weblogs
ai	0	O	weblogs
n't	0	O	weblogs
just	0	O	weblogs
about	0	O	weblogs
strippers	0	O	weblogs
and	0	O	weblogs
dope	0	O	weblogs
.	0	O	weblogs

One	0	O	answers
thing	0	O	answers
you	0	O	answers
can	0	O	answers
be	0	O	answers
sure	0	O	answers
of	0	O	answers
about	0	O	answers
Irish	1	B-LOCderiv	answers
weather	0	O	answers
is	0	O	answers
how	0	O	answers
little	0	O	answers
you	0	O	answers
can	0	O	answers
be	0	O	answers
sure	0	O	answers
of	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

I	0	O	newsgroup
promise	0	O	newsgroup
you	0	O	newsgroup
that	0	O	newsgroup
if	0	O	newsgroup
you	0	O	newsgroup
follow	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
directions	0	O	newsgroup
exactly	0	O	newsgroup
that	0	O	newsgroup
you	0	O	newsgroup
will	0	O	newsgroup
start	0	O	newsgroup
making	0	O	newsgroup
more	0	O	newsgroup
money	0	O	newsgroup
than	0	O	newsgroup
you	0	O	newsgroup
thought	0	O	newsgroup
possible	0	O	newsgroup
by	0	O	newsgroup
doing	0	O	newsgroup
something	0	O	newsgroup
so	0	O	newsgroup
easy	0	O	newsgroup
!!	0	O	newsgroup

he	0	O	answers
's	0	O	answers
just	0	O	answers
a	0	O	answers
tiny	0	O	answers
baby	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
about	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
width	0	O	answers
of	0	O	answers
a	0	O	answers
pencil	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

REAL	0	O	reviews
CHRISTIAN	0	O	reviews
OF	0	O	reviews
YOU	0	O	reviews
!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!	0	O	reviews

The	0	O	newsgroup
problem	0	O	newsgroup
is	0	O	newsgroup
whether	0	O	newsgroup
one	0	O	newsgroup
cares	0	O	newsgroup
what	0	O	newsgroup
happens	0	O	newsgroup
to	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
polar	0	O	newsgroup
bears	0	O	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
checkerspot	0	O	newsgroup
butterflies	0	O	newsgroup
and	0	O	newsgroup
other	0	O	newsgroup
unconsumables	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

Washington	1	B-ORG	newsgroup
would	0	O	newsgroup
really	0	O	newsgroup
have	0	O	newsgroup
to	0	O	newsgroup
anger	0	O	newsgroup
Japan	1	B-ORG	newsgroup
and	0	O	newsgroup
Korea	1	B-ORG	newsgroup
to	0	O	newsgroup
provoke	0	O	newsgroup
such	0	O	newsgroup
action	0	O	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
but	0	O	newsgroup
in	0	O	newsgroup
a	0	O	newsgroup
showdown	0	O	newsgroup
with	0	O	newsgroup
China	1	B-ORG	newsgroup
-	0	O	newsgroup
over	0	O	newsgroup
Taiwan	1	B-LOC	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
for	0	O	newsgroup
example	0	O	newsgroup
-	0	O	newsgroup
China	1	B-ORG	newsgroup
holds	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
cards	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

1	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup
Blowback	0	O	newsgroup
in	0	O	newsgroup
Iraq	1	B-LOC	newsgroup

Although	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
origins	0	O	answers
of	0	O	answers
a	0	O	answers
movement	0	O	answers
that	0	O	answers
was	0	O	answers
confined	0	O	answers
largely	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
literate	0	O	answers
culture	0	O	answers
of	0	O	answers
intellectual	0	O	answers
endeavor	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
patronage	0	O	answers
can	0	O	answers
be	0	O	answers
traced	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
earlier	0	O	answers
part	0	O	answers
of	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
14th	0	O	answers
century	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
many	0	O	answers
aspects	0	O	answers
of	0	O	answers
Italian	1	B-LOCderiv	answers
culture	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
society	0	O	answers
remained	0	O	answers
largely	0	O	answers
Medieval	0	O	answers
;	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
Renaissance	1	B-MISC	answers
did	0	O	answers
not	0	O	answers
come	0	O	answers
into	0	O	answers
full	0	O	answers
swing	0	O	answers
until	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
end	0	O	answers
of	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
century	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

In	0	O	reviews
other	0	O	reviews
words	0	O	reviews
,	0	O	reviews
they	0	O	reviews
do	0	O	reviews
not	0	O	reviews
help	0	O	reviews
with	0	O	reviews
suitcases	0	O	reviews
,	0	O	reviews
but	0	O	reviews
they	0	O	reviews
promise	0	O	reviews
totes	0	O	reviews
to	0	O	reviews
help	0	O	reviews
.	0	O	reviews

I	0	O	email
can	0	O	email
meet	0	O	email
around	0	O	email
10:00	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

scroll	0	O	answers
down	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
this	0	O	answers
website	0	O	answers
shows	0	O	answers
each	0	O	answers
thing	0	O	answers
you	0	O	answers
can	0	O	answers
buy	0	O	answers
(:	0	O	answers

The	0	O	reviews
best	0	O	reviews
there	0	O	reviews
is	0	O	reviews
in	0	O	reviews
service	0	O	reviews
.	0	O	reviews

Dessert	0	O	reviews
was	0	O	reviews
...	0	O	reviews
hmmm	0	O	reviews
,	0	O	reviews
that	0	O	reviews
's	0	O	reviews
interesting	0	O	reviews
,	0	O	reviews
I	0	O	reviews
do	0	O	reviews
n't	0	O	reviews
even	0	O	reviews
remember	0	O	reviews
dessert	0	O	reviews
.	0	O	reviews

This	0	O	email
Friday	0	O	email
-	0	O	email
Michael	1	B-PER	email
goes	0	O	email
for	0	O	email
a	0	O	email
visit	0	O	email
at	0	O	email
St.	1	B-ORG	email
Francis	1	I-ORG	email
,	0	O	email
which	0	O	email
may	0	O	email
be	0	O	email
his	0	O	email
new	0	O	email
school	0	O	email
(	0	O	email
so	0	O	email
far	0	O	email
,	0	O	email
so	0	O	email
good	0	O	email
)	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

Carribbean	1	B-ORG	answers
Bay	1	I-ORG	answers
:	0	O	answers
http://tong.visitkorea.or.kr/cms/resource/81/188181_image2_1.jpg	1	B-MISC	answers

NPR	1	B-ORG	weblogs
's	1	I-ORG	weblogs
Wade	1	B-PER	weblogs
Goodwyn	1	I-PER	weblogs
has	0	O	weblogs
this	0	O	weblogs
report	0	O	weblogs
about	0	O	weblogs
Mr.	0	O	weblogs
Bush	1	B-PER	weblogs
's	1	I-PER	weblogs
time	0	O	weblogs
on	0	O	weblogs
that	0	O	weblogs
campaign	0	O	weblogs
.	0	O	weblogs

Owner	0	O	answers
is	0	O	answers
willing	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
meet	0	O	answers
me	0	O	answers
half	0	O	answers
way	0	O	answers
with	0	O	answers
him	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

There	0	O	newsgroup
are	0	O	newsgroup
only	0	O	newsgroup
about	0	O	newsgroup
850	0	O	newsgroup
wolves	0	O	newsgroup
in	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
West	0	O	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
but	0	O	newsgroup
there	0	O	newsgroup
are	0	O	newsgroup
an	0	O	newsgroup
estimated	0	O	newsgroup
31,000	0	O	newsgroup
mountain	0	O	newsgroup
lions	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

It	0	O	answers
s	0	O	answers
important	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
their	0	O	answers
religion	0	O	answers
that	0	O	answers
they	0	O	answers
only	0	O	answers
consume	0	O	answers
Halal	0	O	answers
food	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

I	0	O	email
assume	0	O	email
you	0	O	email
need	0	O	email
both	0	O	email
gas	0	O	email
and	0	O	email
power	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

fyi	0	O	email
/	0	O	email
review	0	O	email
/	0	O	email
comment	0	O	email

(	0	O	email
Her	0	O	email
voice	0	O	email
mail	0	O	email
says	0	O	email
she	0	O	email
's	0	O	email
out	0	O	email
of	0	O	email
the	0	O	email
office	0	O	email
until	0	O	email
Monday	0	O	email
.	0	O	email
)	0	O	email

and	0	O	newsgroup
a	0	O	newsgroup
good	0	O	newsgroup
reason	0	O	newsgroup
for	0	O	newsgroup
starting	0	O	newsgroup
this	0	O	newsgroup
group	0	O	newsgroup
....	0	O	newsgroup
company	0	O	newsgroup
firewalls	0	O	newsgroup
lol	0	O	newsgroup
;)	0	O	newsgroup

I	0	O	email
just	0	O	email
could	0	O	email
n't	0	O	email
remember	0	O	email
if	0	O	email
it	0	O	email
was	0	O	email
you	0	O	email
or	0	O	email
Terry	1	B-PER	email
.	0	O	email

Also	0	O	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
please	0	O	newsgroup
pass	0	O	newsgroup
this	0	O	newsgroup
along	0	O	newsgroup
to	0	O	newsgroup
everyone	0	O	newsgroup
you	0	O	newsgroup
know	0	O	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
and	0	O	newsgroup
all	0	O	newsgroup
of	0	O	newsgroup
your	0	O	newsgroup
email	0	O	newsgroup
contacts	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

Would	0	O	answers
pledge	0	O	answers
be	0	O	answers
ok	0	O	answers
?	0	O	answers

Thanks	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

<<	0	O	email
MEH-risk	0	O	email
Oct	0	O	email
20	0	O	email
>>	0	O	email

I	0	O	answers
aspire	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
your	0	O	answers
feeding	0	O	answers
regime	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
flakes	0	O	answers
early	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
something	0	O	answers
live	0	O	answers
later	0	O	answers
in	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
day	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

Essie	1	B-PER	email
,	0	O	email

One	0	O	weblogs
of	0	O	weblogs
them	0	O	weblogs
was	0	O	weblogs
from	0	O	weblogs
the	0	O	weblogs
Jubur	1	B-ORG	weblogs
tribe	0	O	weblogs
and	0	O	weblogs
was	0	O	weblogs
deputy	0	O	weblogs
commander	0	O	weblogs
of	0	O	weblogs
the	0	O	weblogs
Hawijah	1	B-ORG	weblogs
garrison	0	O	weblogs
.	0	O	weblogs

David	1	B-PER	email
W	1	I-PER	email
Delainey@ECT	1	I-PER	email

Please	0	O	email
let	0	O	email
me	0	O	email
know	0	O	email
of	0	O	email
your	0	O	email
availability	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

Let	0	O	answers
me	0	O	answers
try	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
break	0	O	answers
this	0	O	answers
down	0	O	answers
as	0	O	answers
simply	0	O	answers
as	0	O	answers
I	0	O	answers
can	0	O	answers
:	0	O	answers
diurnal	0	O	answers
(	0	O	answers
active	0	O	answers
during	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
day	0	O	answers
time	0	O	answers
)	0	O	answers
reptiles	0	O	answers
like	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
bearded	0	O	answers
dragon	0	O	answers
require	0	O	answers
3	0	O	answers
types	0	O	answers
of	0	O	answers
"	0	O	answers
light	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
"	0	O	answers
UVA	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
UVB	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
heat	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

If	0	O	answers
everything	0	O	answers
is	0	O	answers
looking	0	O	answers
good	0	O	answers
you	0	O	answers
may	0	O	answers
add	0	O	answers
you	0	O	answers
betta	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
its	0	O	answers
new	0	O	answers
home	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

Rhonda	1	B-PER	email
L	1	I-PER	email
Denton	1	I-PER	email

The	0	O	answers
chlorine	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
ammonia	0	O	answers
(	0	O	answers
choramine	0	O	answers
)	0	O	answers
are	0	O	answers
not	0	O	answers
good	0	O	answers
for	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
eggs	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

Seems	0	O	weblogs
as	0	O	weblogs
if	0	O	weblogs
there	0	O	weblogs
is	0	O	weblogs
a	0	O	weblogs
clear	0	O	weblogs
distinction	0	O	weblogs
being	0	O	weblogs
made	0	O	weblogs
between	0	O	weblogs
the	0	O	weblogs
'	0	O	weblogs
imaginary	0	O	weblogs
'	0	O	weblogs
Whore	0	O	weblogs
of	0	O	weblogs
Babalon	1	B-LOC	weblogs
and	0	O	weblogs
the	0	O	weblogs
actually	0	O	weblogs
Whore	0	O	weblogs
of	0	O	weblogs
Babylon	1	B-LOC	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
which	0	O	weblogs
is	0	O	weblogs
this	0	O	weblogs
global	0	O	weblogs
system	0	O	weblogs
.	0	O	weblogs

Oh	0	O	answers
my	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
you	0	O	answers
asked	0	O	answers
this	0	O	answers
question	0	O	answers
at	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
perfect	0	O	answers
time	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

Any	0	O	answers
white	0	O	answers
light	0	O	answers
emitting	0	O	answers
light	0	O	answers
source	0	O	answers
will	0	O	answers
emit	0	O	answers
UVA	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
including	0	O	answers
heat	0	O	answers
bulbs	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
that	0	O	answers
's	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
easy	0	O	answers
one	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
provide	0	O	answers
for	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

5	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup
American	1	B-LOCderiv	newsgroup
Preparedness	0	O	newsgroup

Can	0	O	email
we	0	O	email
discuss	0	O	email
this	0	O	email
today	0	O	email
or	0	O	email
soon	0	O	email
thereafter	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

Thanks	0	O	email
,	0	O	email

Talk	0	O	newsgroup
to	0	O	newsgroup
me	0	O	newsgroup
<	0	O	newsgroup
ymsgr:sendIM?mayursha&__Hi+Mayur...	0	O	newsgroup
>	0	O	newsgroup

Overpriced	0	O	reviews

Do	0	O	email
we	0	O	email
want	0	O	email
to	0	O	email
attach	0	O	email
a	0	O	email
draft	0	O	email
of	0	O	email
the	0	O	email
Development	0	O	email
Agreement	0	O	email
,	0	O	email
and	0	O	email
condition	0	O	email
the	0	O	email
final	0	O	email
deal	0	O	email
on	0	O	email
agreeing	0	O	email
to	0	O	email
terms	0	O	email
substantially	0	O	email
the	0	O	email
same	0	O	email
as	0	O	email
what	0	O	email
's	0	O	email
in	0	O	email
the	0	O	email
draft	0	O	email
?	0	O	email

Bumrungrad	1	B-ORG	answers
Hospital	1	I-ORG	answers
does	0	O	answers
some	0	O	answers
good	0	O	answers
work	0	O	answers
but	0	O	answers
all	0	O	answers
hospitals	0	O	answers
do	0	O	answers
have	0	O	answers
their	0	O	answers
problems	0	O	answers
from	0	O	answers
time	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
time	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

Sara	1	B-PER	email
:	0	O	email

Best	0	O	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
Steve	1	B-PER	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

I	0	O	answers
found	0	O	answers
an	0	O	answers
injured	0	O	answers
pure	0	O	answers
white	0	O	answers
bird	0	O	answers
(	0	O	answers
dove	0	O	answers
I	0	O	answers
guess	0	O	answers
?	0	O	answers
)	0	O	answers

select	0	O	email
the	0	O	email
product	0	O	email
requiring	0	O	email
review	0	O	email
as	0	O	email
stated	0	O	email
in	0	O	email
e-mail	0	O	email
above	0	O	email

I	0	O	email
have	0	O	email
a	0	O	email
change	0	O	email
in	0	O	email
plans	0	O	email
next	0	O	email
week	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

the	0	O	email
primary	0	O	email
reason	0	O	email
we	0	O	email
need	0	O	email
these	0	O	email
things	0	O	email
is	0	O	email
for	0	O	email
the	0	O	email
scenario	0	O	email
where	0	O	email
a	0	O	email
muni	0	O	email
does	0	O	email
a	0	O	email
derivative	0	O	email
deal	0	O	email
with	0	O	email
an	0	O	email
open	0	O	email
-	0	O	email
ended	0	O	email
downside	0	O	email
,	0	O	email
loses	0	O	email
$	1	B-MISC	email
50	0	O	email
million	0	O	email
,	0	O	email
and	0	O	email
then	0	O	email
claims	0	O	email
that	0	O	email
it	0	O	email
was	0	O	email
not	0	O	email
a	0	O	email
valid	0	O	email
contract	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

If	0	O	answers
they	0	O	answers
are	0	O	answers
able	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
take	0	O	answers
earthworms	0	O	answers
uncut	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
that	0	O	answers
is	0	O	answers
really	0	O	answers
impressive	0	O	answers
!	0	O	answers

He	0	O	answers
was	0	O	answers
trained	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
a	0	O	answers
harness	0	O	answers
/	0	O	answers
leash	0	O	answers
for	0	O	answers
outside	0	O	answers
time	0	O	answers
but	0	O	answers
he	0	O	answers
knew	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
use	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
litter	0	O	answers
pan	0	O	answers
inside	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

Either	0	O	email
fax	0	O	email
or	0	O	email
someone	0	O	email
else	0	O	email
works	0	O	email
fine	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

Hey	0	O	email
Cester	1	B-PER	email
,	0	O	email

Two	0	O	weblogs
years	0	O	weblogs
.	0	O	weblogs

It	0	O	weblogs
's	0	O	weblogs
become	0	O	weblogs
a	0	O	weblogs
guardian	0	O	weblogs
of	0	O	weblogs
morality	0	O	weblogs
--	0	O	weblogs
not	0	O	weblogs
church	0	O	weblogs
morality	0	O	weblogs
;	0	O	weblogs
real	0	O	weblogs
morality	0	O	weblogs
.	0	O	weblogs

This	0	O	weblogs
formidable	0	O	weblogs
enemy	0	O	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
which	0	O	weblogs
gave	0	O	weblogs
the	0	O	weblogs
Indian	1	B-LOCderiv	weblogs
army	0	O	weblogs
a	0	O	weblogs
black	0	O	weblogs
eye	0	O	weblogs
in	0	O	weblogs
the	0	O	weblogs
mid-1980s	0	O	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
has	0	O	weblogs
been	0	O	weblogs
operating	0	O	weblogs
in	0	O	weblogs
northeastern	0	O	weblogs
India	1	B-LOC	weblogs
and	0	O	weblogs
in	0	O	weblogs
the	0	O	weblogs
Andaman	1	B-LOC	weblogs
Sea	1	I-LOC	weblogs
for	0	O	weblogs
a	0	O	weblogs
long	0	O	weblogs
time	0	O	weblogs
.	0	O	weblogs

You	0	O	answers
only	0	O	answers
got	0	O	answers
him	0	O	answers
yesterday	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

I	0	O	email
was	0	O	email
in	0	O	email
a	0	O	email
meeting	0	O	email
last	0	O	email
week	0	O	email
and	0	O	email
this	0	O	email
was	0	O	email
discussed	0	O	email
(	0	O	email
I	0	O	email
do	0	O	email
n't	0	O	email
remember	0	O	email
if	0	O	email
you	0	O	email
were	0	O	email
there	0	O	email
or	0	O	email
not	0	O	email
)	0	O	email
but	0	O	email
I	0	O	email
'm	0	O	email
thinking	0	O	email
that	0	O	email
you	0	O	email
may	0	O	email
have	0	O	email
already	0	O	email
proceeded	0	O	email
ahead	0	O	email
for	0	O	email
implementation	0	O	email
which	0	O	email
is	0	O	email
great	0	O	email
,	0	O	email
thanks	0	O	email
!	0	O	email

http://news.bbc.co.uk/2/hi/programmes/this_world/4446342.stm	1	B-MISC	weblogs

,	0	O	email
Do	0	O	email
you	0	O	email
want	0	O	email
us	0	O	email
to	0	O	email
come	0	O	email
over	0	O	email
to	0	O	email
the	0	O	email
Enron	1	B-ORG	email
b	0	O	email
in	0	O	email
your	0	O	email
call	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

Please	0	O	answers
help	0	O	answers
me	0	O	answers
!	0	O	answers

It	0	O	email
incorporates	0	O	email
Mr.	0	O	email
Stojic	1	B-PER	email
's	1	I-PER	email
and	0	O	email
Mr.	0	O	email
Kelly	1	B-PER	email
's	1	I-PER	email
initial	0	O	email
comments	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

If	0	O	email
you	0	O	email
got	0	O	email
the	0	O	email
chance	0	O	email
today	0	O	email
,	0	O	email
I	0	O	email
should	0	O	email
be	0	O	email
really	0	O	email
grateful	0	O	email
if	0	O	email
one	0	O	email
of	0	O	email
you	0	O	email
could	0	O	email
give	0	O	email
me	0	O	email
a	0	O	email
call	0	O	email
to	0	O	email
discuss	0	O	email
this	0	O	email
issue	0	O	email
;	0	O	email
I	0	O	email
think	0	O	email
we	0	O	email
should	0	O	email
set	0	O	email
out	0	O	email
DPC	1	B-ORG	email
's	1	B-ORG	email
position	0	O	email
clearly	0	O	email
on	0	O	email
this	0	O	email
in	0	O	email
correspondence	0	O	email
without	0	O	email
too	0	O	email
much	0	O	email
delay	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

Bill	1	B-PER	email
-	0	O	email

I	0	O	email
am	0	O	email
vacation	0	O	email
until	0	O	email
the	0	O	email
22nd	0	O	email
but	0	O	email
Per	1	B-PER	email
is	0	O	email
up	0	O	email
to	0	O	email
speed	0	O	email
and	0	O	email
I	0	O	email
would	0	O	email
like	0	O	email
to	0	O	email
make	0	O	email
sure	0	O	email
that	0	O	email
you	0	O	email
keep	0	O	email
up	0	O	email
with	0	O	email
him	0	O	email
and	0	O	email
any	0	O	email
HR	0	O	email
/	0	O	email
Legal	0	O	email
activity	0	O	email
that	0	O	email
may	0	O	email
occur	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

The	0	O	reviews
U	1	B-ORG	reviews
of	1	I-ORG	reviews
R	1	I-ORG	reviews
is	0	O	reviews
also	0	O	reviews
recommended	0	O	reviews
,	0	O	reviews
too	0	O	reviews
!	0	O	reviews

All	0	O	reviews
the	0	O	reviews
food	0	O	reviews
tasted	0	O	reviews
excellent	0	O	reviews
,	0	O	reviews
and	0	O	reviews
with	0	O	reviews
the	0	O	reviews
new	0	O	reviews
renovation	0	O	reviews
of	0	O	reviews
chairs	0	O	reviews
and	0	O	reviews
the	0	O	reviews
bathroom	0	O	reviews
,	0	O	reviews
it	0	O	reviews
is	0	O	reviews
awesome	0	O	reviews
.	0	O	reviews

Floating	0	O	email
Amount	0	O	email
=	0	O	email
(	0	O	email
Notional	0	O	email
Quantity	0	O	email
per	0	O	email
Calculation	0	O	email
Period	0	O	email
X	0	O	email
Floating	0	O	email
Price	0	O	email
)	0	O	email
-	0	O	email
USD	1	B-MISC	email
[	0	O	email
38,000	0	O	email
?	0	O	email
]	0	O	email

Also	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
do	0	O	answers
n't	0	O	answers
forget	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
try	0	O	answers
out	0	O	answers
Korea	1	B-LOC	answers
's	1	I-LOC	answers
famous	0	O	answers
amusement	0	O	answers
parks	0	O	answers
!	0	O	answers
:	0	O	answers
Lotte	1	B-ORG	answers
World	1	I-ORG	answers
,	0	O	answers
Everland	1	B-ORG	answers
,	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
Carribbean	1	B-ORG	answers
Bay	1	I-ORG	answers
!	0	O	answers

The	0	O	reviews
ability	0	O	reviews
to	0	O	reviews
smile	0	O	reviews
and	0	O	reviews
eat	0	O	reviews
again	0	O	reviews
can	0	O	reviews
only	0	O	reviews
be	0	O	reviews
described	0	O	reviews
as	0	O	reviews
a	0	O	reviews
whole	0	O	reviews
new	0	O	reviews
lease	0	O	reviews
on	0	O	reviews
life	0	O	reviews
.	0	O	reviews

I	0	O	reviews
had	0	O	reviews
a	0	O	reviews
surgery	0	O	reviews
date	0	O	reviews
of	0	O	reviews
July	0	O	reviews
17	0	O	reviews
,	0	O	reviews
2008	0	O	reviews
.	0	O	reviews

But	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
can	0	O	answers
you	0	O	answers
immigrate	0	O	answers
?	0	O	answers

Hi	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
I	0	O	answers
am	0	O	answers
a	0	O	answers
dog	0	O	answers
trainer	0	O	answers
for	0	O	answers
25	0	O	answers
yrs	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

http://www.csmonitor.com/2006/0509/p02s01-ussc.html?s=t5	1	B-MISC	weblogs

Please	0	O	email
review	0	O	email
the	0	O	email
process	0	O	email
below	0	O	email
:	0	O	email

I	0	O	answers
would	0	O	answers
really	0	O	answers
love	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
hear	0	O	answers
what	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
French	1	B-LOCderiv	answers
or	0	O	answers
those	0	O	answers
who	0	O	answers
had	0	O	answers
dated	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
French	1	B-LOCderiv	answers
to	0	O	answers
say	0	O	answers
something	0	O	answers
about	0	O	answers
this	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

All	0	O	email
Evaluations	0	O	email
for	0	O	email
Associates	0	O	email
and	0	O	email
Analysts	0	O	email
must	0	O	email
be	0	O	email
completed	0	O	email
using	0	O	email
this	0	O	email
form	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

Any	0	O	email
GCP	1	B-MISC	email
adjustments	0	O	email
will	0	O	email
be	0	O	email
highlighted	0	O	email
in	0	O	email
red	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

Service	0	O	reviews
was	0	O	reviews
excellent	0	O	reviews
.	0	O	reviews

The	0	O	reviews
store	0	O	reviews
is	0	O	reviews
clean	0	O	reviews
,	0	O	reviews
run	0	O	reviews
very	0	O	reviews
professionally	0	O	reviews
and	0	O	reviews
a	0	O	reviews
pleasure	0	O	reviews
to	0	O	reviews
be	0	O	reviews
in	0	O	reviews
.	0	O	reviews

http://www.flickr.com/photos/adamtolle/6094960940/in/set-72157627535453128/	1	B-MISC	answers

According	0	O	weblogs
to	0	O	weblogs
records	0	O	weblogs
released	0	O	weblogs
earlier	0	O	weblogs
this	0	O	weblogs
year	0	O	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
Bush	1	B-PER	weblogs
earned	0	O	weblogs
253	0	O	weblogs
points	0	O	weblogs
in	0	O	weblogs
his	0	O	weblogs
first	0	O	weblogs
year	0	O	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
May	0	O	weblogs
1968	0	O	weblogs
to	0	O	weblogs
May	0	O	weblogs
1969	0	O	weblogs
(	0	O	weblogs
since	0	O	weblogs
he	0	O	weblogs
joined	0	O	weblogs
in	0	O	weblogs
May	0	O	weblogs
1968	0	O	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
his	0	O	weblogs
service	0	O	weblogs
thereafter	0	O	weblogs
was	0	O	weblogs
measured	0	O	weblogs
on	0	O	weblogs
a	0	O	weblogs
May	0	O	weblogs
-	0	O	weblogs
to	0	O	weblogs
-	0	O	weblogs
May	0	O	weblogs
basis	0	O	weblogs
)	0	O	weblogs
.	0	O	weblogs

That	0	O	reviews
said	0	O	reviews
-	0	O	reviews
he	0	O	reviews
seemed	0	O	reviews
to	0	O	reviews
be	0	O	reviews
doing	0	O	reviews
well	0	O	reviews
enough	0	O	reviews
.	0	O	reviews

Tana	1	B-PER	email
,	0	O	email

Bearded	0	O	answers
dragon	0	O	answers
question	0	O	answers
...	0	O	answers
?	0	O	answers

I	0	O	email
leave	0	O	email
the	0	O	email
evening	0	O	email
of	0	O	email
the	0	O	email
21st	0	O	email
,	0	O	email
my	0	O	email
flight	0	O	email
comes	0	O	email
in	0	O	email
about	0	O	email
10	0	O	email
pm	0	O	email
,	0	O	email
and	0	O	email
leave	0	O	email
the	0	O	email
morning	0	O	email
of	0	O	email
the	0	O	email
27th	0	O	email
at	0	O	email
6	0	O	email
am	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

Should	0	O	answers
all	0	O	answers
UK	1	B-LOCderiv	answers
towns	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
their	0	O	answers
cafes	0	O	answers
or	0	O	answers
restaurants	0	O	answers
provide	0	O	answers
Halal	0	O	answers
food	0	O	answers
?	0	O	answers

@	0	O	answers
Ryan	1	B-PER	answers
B	1	I-PER	answers
,	0	O	answers

So	0	O	weblogs
...	0	O	weblogs
put	0	O	weblogs
some	0	O	weblogs
information	0	O	weblogs
in	0	O	weblogs
there	0	O	weblogs
.	0	O	weblogs

Because	0	O	reviews
we	0	O	reviews
think	0	O	reviews
IT	0	O	reviews
'S	0	O	reviews
THE	0	O	reviews
BEST	0	O	reviews
!!!	0	O	reviews

"	0	O	weblogs
The	0	O	weblogs
Prophet	0	O	weblogs
's	0	O	weblogs
guidance	0	O	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
"	0	O	weblogs
says	0	O	weblogs
Michael	1	B-PER	weblogs
Scheuer	1	I-PER	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
an	0	O	weblogs
al	1	B-ORG	weblogs
-	1	I-ORG	weblogs
Qaeda	1	I-ORG	weblogs
analyst	0	O	weblogs
who	0	O	weblogs
recently	0	O	weblogs
retired	0	O	weblogs
from	0	O	weblogs
the	0	O	weblogs
CIA	1	B-ORG	weblogs
and	0	O	weblogs
once	0	O	weblogs
headed	0	O	weblogs
its	0	O	weblogs
Bin	1	B-PER	weblogs
Laden	1	I-PER	weblogs
unit	0	O	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
"	0	O	weblogs
was	0	O	weblogs
always	0	O	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
Before	0	O	weblogs
you	0	O	weblogs
attack	0	O	weblogs
someone	0	O	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
warn	0	O	weblogs
them	0	O	weblogs
very	0	O	weblogs
clearly	0	O	weblogs
...	0	O	weblogs
"	0	O	weblogs
The	0	O	weblogs
anthrax	0	O	weblogs
mailings	0	O	weblogs
followed	0	O	weblogs
the	0	O	weblogs
pattern	0	O	weblogs
of	0	O	weblogs
letters	0	O	weblogs
they	0	O	weblogs
sent	0	O	weblogs
in	0	O	weblogs
January	0	O	weblogs
1997	0	O	weblogs
to	0	O	weblogs
newspaper	0	O	weblogs
branches	0	O	weblogs
in	0	O	weblogs
Washington	1	B-LOC	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
D.C.	1	B-LOC	weblogs
and	0	O	weblogs
New	1	B-LOC	weblogs
York	1	I-LOC	weblogs
City	1	I-LOC	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
as	0	O	weblogs
well	0	O	weblogs
as	0	O	weblogs
symbolic	0	O	weblogs
targets	0	O	weblogs
.	0	O	weblogs

I	0	O	reviews
had	0	O	reviews
to	0	O	reviews
take	0	O	reviews
care	0	O	reviews
of	0	O	reviews
the	0	O	reviews
ants	0	O	reviews
myself	0	O	reviews
.	0	O	reviews

Game	0	O	email
14	0	O	email
:	0	O	email
Friday	0	O	email
,	0	O	email
August	0	O	email
3	0	O	email
@	0	O	email
7:30	0	O	email
PM	0	O	email
vs.	0	O	email
Orlando	1	B-ORG	email
MIRACLE	1	I-ORG	email

The	0	O	answers
ARVN	1	B-ORG	answers
was	0	O	answers
not	0	O	answers
having	0	O	answers
a	0	O	answers
big	0	O	answers
problem	0	O	answers
with	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
Local	0	O	answers
VC	1	B-ORG	answers
(	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
guerilla	0	O	answers
movement	0	O	answers
)	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
they	0	O	answers
were	0	O	answers
being	0	O	answers
challenged	0	O	answers
by	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
Main	1	B-ORG	answers
Force	1	I-ORG	answers
VC	1	I-ORG	answers
(	0	O	answers
which	0	O	answers
was	0	O	answers
light	0	O	answers
infantry	0	O	answers
)	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
North	1	B-ORG	answers
Vietnamese	1	I-ORG	answers
Army	1	I-ORG	answers
(	0	O	answers
NVA	1	B-ORG	answers
)	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

I	0	O	reviews
have	0	O	reviews
been	0	O	reviews
here	0	O	reviews
before	0	O	reviews
and	0	O	reviews
the	0	O	reviews
service	0	O	reviews
was	0	O	reviews
absoulutely	0	O	reviews
great	0	O	reviews
.	0	O	reviews

Sheila	1	B-PER	email
Knudsen	1	I-PER	email

But	0	O	reviews
she	0	O	reviews
did	0	O	reviews
a	0	O	reviews
fabulous	0	O	reviews
job	0	O	reviews
letting	0	O	reviews
me	0	O	reviews
know	0	O	reviews
what	0	O	reviews
she	0	O	reviews
was	0	O	reviews
doing	0	O	reviews
at	0	O	reviews
all	0	O	reviews
times	0	O	reviews
and	0	O	reviews
styled	0	O	reviews
my	0	O	reviews
hair	0	O	reviews
in	0	O	reviews
a	0	O	reviews
way	0	O	reviews
i	0	O	reviews
could	0	O	reviews
do	0	O	reviews
it	0	O	reviews
at	0	O	reviews
home	0	O	reviews
.	0	O	reviews

http://www.guardian.co.uk/obituaries/story/0,3604,1371372,00.html	1	B-MISC	weblogs

Please	0	O	email
find	0	O	email
attached	0	O	email
the	0	O	email
Enron	1	B-PER	email
Master	0	O	email
Agreement	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

I	0	O	answers
think	0	O	answers
I	0	O	answers
gained	0	O	answers
three	0	O	answers
pounds	0	O	answers
in	0	O	answers
my	0	O	answers
week	0	O	answers
long	0	O	answers
cruise	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

I	0	O	weblogs
thought	0	O	weblogs
it	0	O	weblogs
unusual	0	O	weblogs
and	0	O	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
frankly	0	O	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
inappropriate	0	O	weblogs
.	0	O	weblogs

Like	0	O	reviews
the	0	O	reviews
girl	0	O	reviews
with	0	O	reviews
the	0	O	reviews
fuse	0	O	reviews
problem	0	O	reviews
...	0	O	reviews

or	0	O	answers
is	0	O	answers
he	0	O	answers
Not	0	O	answers
your	0	O	answers
type	0	O	answers
?	0	O	answers

In	0	O	newsgroup
10	0	O	newsgroup
more	0	O	newsgroup
years	0	O	newsgroup
we	0	O	newsgroup
'll	0	O	newsgroup
have	0	O	newsgroup
a	0	O	newsgroup
better	0	O	newsgroup
idea	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup
"	0	O	newsgroup

So	0	O	reviews
my	0	O	reviews
advice	0	O	reviews
is	0	O	reviews
that	0	O	reviews
NEVER	0	O	reviews
TRUST	0	O	reviews
THIS	0	O	reviews
DEALER	0	O	reviews
.	0	O	reviews

It	0	O	answers
s	0	O	answers
Really	0	O	answers
Good	0	O	answers
And	0	O	answers
The	0	O	answers
Rat	1	B-MISC	answers
Calculater	1	I-MISC	answers
Says	0	O	answers
Is	0	O	answers
Big	0	O	answers
Enough	0	O	answers
For	0	O	answers
5	0	O	answers
Rats	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
But	0	O	answers
I	0	O	answers
Would	0	O	answers
Put	0	O	answers
A	0	O	answers
Maximum	0	O	answers
Of	0	O	answers
4	0	O	answers
In	0	O	answers
It	0	O	answers
Really	0	O	answers
:)	0	O	answers

Here	0	O	newsgroup
is	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
ideation	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

(	0	O	email
Please	0	O	email
visit	0	O	email
our	0	O	email
newly	0	O	email
updated	0	O	email
website	0	O	email
www.caem.org	1	B-MISC	email
for	0	O	email
more	0	O	email
information	0	O	email
on	0	O	email
the	0	O	email
DISCO	1	B-ORG	email
Forum	1	I-ORG	email
.	0	O	email
)	0	O	email

Loads	0	O	answers
of	0	O	answers
places	0	O	answers
have	0	O	answers
geographical	0	O	answers
hazards	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
if	0	O	answers
you	0	O	answers
are	0	O	answers
constantly	0	O	answers
paranoid	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
you	0	O	answers
'll	0	O	answers
never	0	O	answers
get	0	O	answers
anywhere	0	O	answers
without	0	O	answers
a	0	O	answers
sense	0	O	answers
of	0	O	answers
adventure	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

Best	0	O	email
regards	0	O	email
,	0	O	email

Canned	0	O	answers
food	0	O	answers
is	0	O	answers
often	0	O	answers
suspect	0	O	answers
as	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
actual	0	O	answers
contents	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
you	0	O	answers
're	0	O	answers
paying	0	O	answers
for	0	O	answers
a	0	O	answers
high	0	O	answers
moisture	0	O	answers
content	0	O	answers
instead	0	O	answers
of	0	O	answers
food	0	O	answers
content	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

Please	0	O	email
let	0	O	email
me	0	O	email
know	0	O	email
if	0	O	email
any	0	O	email
of	0	O	email
you	0	O	email
need	0	O	email
additional	0	O	email
information	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

The	0	O	email
liq	0	O	email
value	0	O	email
for	0	O	email
the	0	O	email
call	0	O	email
is	0	O	email
CORRECT	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

The	0	O	newsgroup
bear	0	O	newsgroup
ran	0	O	newsgroup
off	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

It	0	O	answers
is	0	O	answers
a	0	O	answers
curb	0	O	answers
bit	0	O	answers
with	0	O	answers
a	0	O	answers
ported	0	O	answers
mouth	0	O	answers
piece	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
some	0	O	answers
horses	0	O	answers
appreciate	0	O	answers
this	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
give	0	O	answers
them	0	O	answers
more	0	O	answers
room	0	O	answers
in	0	O	answers
their	0	O	answers
mouths	0	O	answers
for	0	O	answers
their	0	O	answers
tongues	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

That	0	O	reviews
being	0	O	reviews
said	0	O	reviews
,	0	O	reviews
I	0	O	reviews
do	0	O	reviews
n't	0	O	reviews
know	0	O	reviews
how	0	O	reviews
their	0	O	reviews
delivery	0	O	reviews
service	0	O	reviews
is	0	O	reviews
.	0	O	reviews

Bill	1	B-PER	email
D	1	I-PER	email
Hare	1	I-PER	email

News	0	O	weblogs
coverage	0	O	weblogs
of	0	O	weblogs
the	0	O	weblogs
president	0	O	weblogs
’s	0	O	weblogs
years	0	O	weblogs
in	0	O	weblogs
the	0	O	weblogs
Guard	1	B-ORG	weblogs
has	0	O	weblogs
tended	0	O	weblogs
to	0	O	weblogs
focus	0	O	weblogs
on	0	O	weblogs
one	0	O	weblogs
brief	0	O	weblogs
portion	0	O	weblogs
of	0	O	weblogs
that	0	O	weblogs
time	0	O	weblogs
—	0	O	weblogs
to	0	O	weblogs
the	0	O	weblogs
exclusion	0	O	weblogs
of	0	O	weblogs
virtually	0	O	weblogs
everything	0	O	weblogs
else	0	O	weblogs
.	0	O	weblogs

Kim	1	B-PER	email
.	0	O	email

Never	0	O	reviews
again	0	O	reviews

Hope	0	O	answers
you	0	O	answers
unde$tood	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
me$$age	0	O	answers
I	0	O	answers
do	0	O	answers
have	0	O	answers
an	0	O	answers
"	0	O	answers
S	0	O	answers
"	0	O	answers
key	0	O	answers
on	0	O	answers
my	0	O	answers
computer	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

He	0	O	answers
can	0	O	answers
eat	0	O	answers
grain	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
I	0	O	answers
already	0	O	answers
have	0	O	answers
a	0	O	answers
feed	0	O	answers
regimen	0	O	answers
in	0	O	answers
my	0	O	answers
head	0	O	answers
for	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
guy	0	O	answers
since	0	O	answers
he	0	O	answers
ca	0	O	answers
n't	0	O	answers
eat	0	O	answers
regular	0	O	answers
hay	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

Doctor	0	O	reviews
Gonzales	1	B-PER	reviews
and	0	O	reviews
his	0	O	reviews
entire	0	O	reviews
staff	0	O	reviews
are	0	O	reviews
the	0	O	reviews
most	0	O	reviews
professional	0	O	reviews
people	0	O	reviews
I	0	O	reviews
have	0	O	reviews
ever	0	O	reviews
dealt	0	O	reviews
with	0	O	reviews
.	0	O	reviews

Kay	1	B-PER	email

Clayton	1	B-PER	email

And	0	O	answers
do	0	O	answers
n't	0	O	answers
expect	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
party	0	O	answers
on	0	O	answers
this	0	O	answers
tour	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

Thane	1	B-PER	email
is	0	O	email
in	0	O	email
an	0	O	email
Ercot	1	B-ORG	email
PRS	1	I-ORG	email
meeting	0	O	email
Friday	0	O	email
from	0	O	email
9:30	0	O	email
until	0	O	email
3:00	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

All	0	O	reviews
I	0	O	reviews
can	0	O	reviews
say	0	O	reviews
is	0	O	reviews
that	0	O	reviews
I	0	O	reviews
am	0	O	reviews
glad	0	O	reviews
I	0	O	reviews
went	0	O	reviews
in	0	O	reviews
!	0	O	reviews

In	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
decade	0	O	newsgroup
of	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
nineteen	0	O	newsgroup
-	0	O	newsgroup
eighties	0	O	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
my	0	O	newsgroup
father	0	O	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
then	0	O	newsgroup
vice	0	O	newsgroup
-	0	O	newsgroup
president	0	O	newsgroup
of	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
United	1	B-LOC	newsgroup
States	1	I-LOC	newsgroup
of	1	I-LOC	newsgroup
America	1	I-LOC	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
sought	0	O	newsgroup
to	0	O	newsgroup
work	0	O	newsgroup
with	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
good	0	O	newsgroup
offices	0	O	newsgroup
of	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
President	0	O	newsgroup
of	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
Republic	1	B-LOC	newsgroup
of	1	I-LOC	newsgroup
Iraq	1	I-LOC	newsgroup
to	0	O	newsgroup
regain	0	O	newsgroup
lost	0	O	newsgroup
oil	0	O	newsgroup
revenue	0	O	newsgroup
sources	0	O	newsgroup
in	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
neighboring	0	O	newsgroup
Islamic	1	B-LOC	newsgroup
republic	1	I-LOC	newsgroup
of	1	I-LOC	newsgroup
Iran	1	I-LOC	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

The	0	O	reviews
place	0	O	reviews
is	0	O	reviews
chill	0	O	reviews
and	0	O	reviews
comfortable	0	O	reviews
.	0	O	reviews

I	0	O	email
have	0	O	email
a	0	O	email
few	0	O	email
entities	0	O	email
that	0	O	email
may	0	O	email
need	0	O	email
to	0	O	email
change	0	O	email
groups	0	O	email
or	0	O	email
be	0	O	email
assigned	0	O	email
to	0	O	email
a	0	O	email
group	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

Lora	1	B-PER	email
Sullivan	1	I-PER	email
Federal	0	O	email
Government	0	O	email
Affairs	0	O	email
Representative	0	O	email
Enron	1	B-ORG	email
1775	0	O	email
Eye	1	B-LOC	email
Street	1	I-LOC	email
,	0	O	email
NW	0	O	email
Suite	0	O	email
800	0	O	email
Washington	1	B-LOC	email
,	0	O	email
DC	1	B-LOC	email
20006	0	O	email
202-466-9142	0	O	email
202-828-3372	0	O	email
(	0	O	email
fax	0	O	email
)	0	O	email
email	0	O	email
:	0	O	email
lora.sullivan@enron.com	1	B-PER	email

or	0	O	answers
do	0	O	answers
i	0	O	answers
just	0	O	answers
show	0	O	answers
them	0	O	answers
passport	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
walk	0	O	answers
through	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
gates	0	O	answers
?	0	O	answers

"	0	O	newsgroup
Iran	1	B-ORG	newsgroup
has	0	O	newsgroup
significant	0	O	newsgroup
capabilities	0	O	newsgroup
for	0	O	newsgroup
asymmetric	0	O	newsgroup
warfare	0	O	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
and	0	O	newsgroup
poses	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
additional	0	O	newsgroup
threat	0	O	newsgroup
of	0	O	newsgroup
proliferation	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

Sectarian	0	O	weblogs
tensions	0	O	weblogs
are	0	O	weblogs
at	0	O	weblogs
their	0	O	weblogs
highest	0	O	weblogs
since	0	O	weblogs
April	0	O	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
2004	0	O	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
with	0	O	weblogs
Sunni	0	O	weblogs
insurgents	0	O	weblogs
now	0	O	weblogs
openly	0	O	weblogs
attacking	0	O	weblogs
Husseiniyas	1	B-PERderiv	weblogs
and	0	O	weblogs
Shia	0	O	weblogs
mosques	0	O	weblogs
.	0	O	weblogs

They	0	O	email
are	0	O	email
a	0	O	email
great	0	O	email
deal	0	O	email
of	0	O	email
fun	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

Flipped	0	O	reviews
the	0	O	reviews
square	0	O	reviews
over	0	O	reviews
and	0	O	reviews
saw	0	O	reviews
it	0	O	reviews
riddled	0	O	reviews
with	0	O	reviews
green	0	O	reviews
mold	0	O	reviews
!!!!	0	O	reviews

It	0	O	answers
had	0	O	answers
better	0	O	answers
nutritional	0	O	answers
value	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
it	0	O	answers
s	0	O	answers
also	0	O	answers
less	0	O	answers
expensive	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

why	0	O	answers
do	0	O	answers
nt	0	O	answers
you	0	O	answers
get	0	O	answers
some	0	O	answers
treats	0	O	answers
that	0	O	answers
he	0	O	answers
loves	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
only	0	O	answers
give	0	O	answers
him	0	O	answers
them	0	O	answers
when	0	O	answers
he	0	O	answers
does	0	O	answers
something	0	O	answers
right	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

Came	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
disintegration	0	O	newsgroup
of	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
Beatles	1	B-ORG	newsgroup
'	0	O	newsgroup
minds	0	O	newsgroup
with	0	O	newsgroup
LSD	0	O	newsgroup
which	0	O	newsgroup
has	0	O	newsgroup
caused	0	O	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
among	0	O	newsgroup
others	0	O	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
schizophrenic	0	O	newsgroup
lyrics	0	O	newsgroup
such	0	O	newsgroup
as	0	O	newsgroup
"	0	O	newsgroup
I	0	O	newsgroup
am	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
Walrus	0	O	newsgroup
"	0	O	newsgroup
and	0	O	newsgroup
incoherent	0	O	newsgroup
schizophrenic	0	O	newsgroup
musical	0	O	newsgroup
expositions	0	O	newsgroup
like	0	O	newsgroup
"	0	O	newsgroup
Revolution	1	B-MISC	newsgroup
number	1	I-MISC	newsgroup
9	1	I-MISC	newsgroup
"	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

Whatever	0	O	answers
you	0	O	answers
do	0	O	answers
...............	0	O	answers
DO	0	O	answers
NOT	0	O	answers
try	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
come	0	O	answers
here	0	O	answers
with	0	O	answers
out	0	O	answers
legal	0	O	answers
permission	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

Almost	0	O	email
done	0	O	email
with	0	O	email
your	0	O	email
drafts	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

You	0	O	answers
may	0	O	answers
also	0	O	answers
want	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
avoid	0	O	answers
Thanksgiving	0	O	answers
week	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
Christmas	0	O	answers
holidays	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

This	0	O	email
financing	0	O	email
activity	0	O	email
was	0	O	email
primarily	0	O	email
started	0	O	email
to	0	O	email
help	0	O	email
ENA	1	B-ORG	email
secure	0	O	email
long	0	O	email
term	0	O	email
well	0	O	email
head	0	O	email
and	0	O	email
pipeline	0	O	email
natural	0	O	email
gas	0	O	email
supplies	0	O	email
to	0	O	email
supplement	0	O	email
the	0	O	email
gas	0	O	email
trading	0	O	email
desk	0	O	email
activities	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

Cindy	1	B-PER	email
said	0	O	email
Jaime	1	B-PER	email
has	0	O	email
grown	0	O	email
up	0	O	email
very	0	O	email
much	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

[	0	O	answers
1	0	O	answers
]	0	O	answers
Over	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
last	0	O	answers
twenty	0	O	answers
years	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
use	0	O	answers
of	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
term	0	O	answers
has	0	O	answers
been	0	O	answers
frequently	0	O	answers
criticized	0	O	answers
by	0	O	answers
academic	0	O	answers
art	0	O	answers
historians	0	O	answers
for	0	O	answers
over-simplifying	0	O	answers
artistic	0	O	answers
developments	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
ignoring	0	O	answers
historical	0	O	answers
context	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
focusing	0	O	answers
only	0	O	answers
on	0	O	answers
a	0	O	answers
few	0	O	answers
iconic	0	O	answers
works	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

Sent	0	O	email
by	0	O	email
:	0	O	email
Nella	1	B-PER	email
Cappelletto	1	I-PER	email

A	0	O	newsgroup
health	0	O	newsgroup
-	0	O	newsgroup
conscious	0	O	newsgroup
president	0	O	newsgroup

The	0	O	email
application	0	O	email
of	0	O	email
recent	0	O	email
developments	0	O	email
in	0	O	email
optimization	0	O	email
theory	0	O	email
and	0	O	email
numerical	0	O	email
methods	0	O	email
can	0	O	email
help	0	O	email
Enron	1	B-ORG	email
to	0	O	email
improve	0	O	email
further	0	O	email
efficiency	0	O	email
of	0	O	email
our	0	O	email
pipeline	0	O	email
system	0	O	email
and	0	O	email
reduce	0	O	email
the	0	O	email
consumption	0	O	email
of	0	O	email
compressor	0	O	email
fuel	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

CRACKDOWN	0	O	weblogs
ON	0	O	weblogs
POLYGAMY	0	O	weblogs
GROUP	0	O	weblogs

My	0	O	answers
breyers	1	B-ORGderiv	answers
need	0	O	answers
stables	0	O	answers
or	0	O	answers
barns	0	O	answers
though	0	O	answers
.....	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
I	0	O	answers
need	0	O	answers
directions	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
materials	0	O	answers
on	0	O	answers
how	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
make	0	O	answers
them	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

He	0	O	weblogs
is	0	O	weblogs
no	0	O	weblogs
longer	0	O	weblogs
in	0	O	weblogs
the	0	O	weblogs
dominant	0	O	weblogs
Shiite	0	O	weblogs
list	0	O	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
the	0	O	weblogs
United	1	B-ORG	weblogs
Iraqi	1	I-ORG	weblogs
Alliance	1	I-ORG	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
and	0	O	weblogs
wo	0	O	weblogs
n't	0	O	weblogs
have	0	O	weblogs
many	0	O	weblogs
seats	0	O	weblogs
in	0	O	weblogs
the	0	O	weblogs
new	0	O	weblogs
parliament	0	O	weblogs
.	0	O	weblogs

Richard	1	B-PER	email
-	0	O	email
please	0	O	email
let	0	O	email
me	0	O	email
know	0	O	email
what	0	O	email
we	0	O	email
need	0	O	email
to	0	O	email
do	0	O	email
next	0	O	email
to	0	O	email
file	0	O	email
suit	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

What	0	O	email
power	0	O	email
curve	0	O	email
are	0	O	email
we	0	O	email
valuing	0	O	email
the	0	O	email
deal	0	O	email
against	0	O	email
-	0	O	email
PJM	1	B-MISC	email
East	1	I-MISC	email
or	0	O	email
West	1	B-MISC	email
Hub	1	I-MISC	email
?	0	O	email

I	0	O	answers
've	0	O	answers
been	0	O	answers
given	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
opportunity	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
live	0	O	answers
in	0	O	answers
Limerick	1	B-LOC	answers
,	0	O	answers
Ireland	1	B-LOC	answers
,	0	O	answers
next	0	O	answers
year	0	O	answers
as	0	O	answers
part	0	O	answers
of	0	O	answers
my	0	O	answers
course	0	O	answers
..	0	O	answers
if	0	O	answers
you	0	O	answers
know	0	O	answers
about	0	O	answers
Limerick	1	B-LOC	answers
,	0	O	answers
what	0	O	answers
are	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
pros	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
cons	0	O	answers
?	0	O	answers

I	0	O	newsgroup
was	0	O	newsgroup
beside	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
bear	0	O	newsgroup
's	0	O	newsgroup
head	0	O	newsgroup
and	0	O	newsgroup
I	0	O	newsgroup
stabbed	0	O	newsgroup
it	0	O	newsgroup
with	0	O	newsgroup
an	0	O	newsgroup
upper	0	O	newsgroup
cut	0	O	newsgroup
below	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
jaw	0	O	newsgroup
in	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
neck	0	O	newsgroup
a	0	O	newsgroup
couple	0	O	newsgroup
of	0	O	newsgroup
times	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup
"	0	O	newsgroup

[	0	O	newsgroup
]	0	O	newsgroup

1983	0	O	newsgroup
-	0	O	newsgroup
The	0	O	newsgroup
year	0	O	newsgroup
in	0	O	newsgroup
which	0	O	newsgroup
Donald	1	B-PER	newsgroup
Rumsfeld	1	I-PER	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
Ronald	1	B-PER	newsgroup
Reagan	1	I-PER	newsgroup
's	1	I-PER	newsgroup
special	0	O	newsgroup
envoy	0	O	newsgroup
to	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
Middle	1	B-LOC	newsgroup
East	1	I-LOC	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
gave	0	O	newsgroup
Saddam	1	B-PER	newsgroup
Hussein	1	I-PER	newsgroup
a	0	O	newsgroup
pair	0	O	newsgroup
of	0	O	newsgroup
golden	0	O	newsgroup
spurs	0	O	newsgroup
as	0	O	newsgroup
a	0	O	newsgroup
gift	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

They	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
too	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
need	0	O	answers
weekly	0	O	answers
cage	0	O	answers
cleaning	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
can	0	O	answers
cost	0	O	answers
quite	0	O	answers
a	0	O	answers
bit	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

As	0	O	email
always	0	O	email
,	0	O	email
thank	0	O	email
you	0	O	email
for	0	O	email
your	0	O	email
time	0	O	email
and	0	O	email
please	0	O	email
contact	0	O	email
me	0	O	email
@	0	O	email
ext	0	O	email
58369	0	O	email
if	0	O	email
you	0	O	email
have	0	O	email
any	0	O	email
questions	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

Parakeet	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

If	0	O	email
we	0	O	email
are	0	O	email
covered	0	O	email
,	0	O	email
then	0	O	email
was	0	O	email
it	0	O	email
necessary	0	O	email
to	0	O	email
register	0	O	email
EnronOnline	1	B-MISC	email
?	0	O	email

sort	0	O	answers
a	0	O	answers
wonder	0	O	answers
what	0	O	answers
it	0	O	answers
would	0	O	answers
have	0	O	answers
been	0	O	answers
like	0	O	answers
?	0	O	answers

For	0	O	answers
more	0	O	answers
info	0	O	answers
on	0	O	answers
lo	0	O	answers
-	0	O	answers
fi	0	O	answers
photography	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
check	0	O	answers
put	0	O	answers
my	0	O	answers
website	0	O	answers
:	0	O	answers

But	0	O	newsgroup
as	0	O	newsgroup
its	0	O	newsgroup
economy	0	O	newsgroup
has	0	O	newsgroup
expanded	0	O	newsgroup
by	0	O	newsgroup
an	0	O	newsgroup
average	0	O	newsgroup
of	0	O	newsgroup
nine	0	O	newsgroup
per	0	O	newsgroup
cent	0	O	newsgroup
per	0	O	newsgroup
year	0	O	newsgroup
for	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
last	0	O	newsgroup
two	0	O	newsgroup
decades	0	O	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
so	0	O	newsgroup
has	0	O	newsgroup
its	0	O	newsgroup
demand	0	O	newsgroup
for	0	O	newsgroup
energy	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

This	0	O	email
defeats	0	O	email
the	0	O	email
purpose	0	O	email
of	0	O	email
using	0	O	email
a	0	O	email
Tradename	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

He	0	O	email
is	0	O	email
joining	0	O	email
an	0	O	email
excellent	0	O	email
company	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

Ifa	1	B-ORG	reviews
is	0	O	reviews
an	0	O	reviews
acronym	0	O	reviews
for	0	O	reviews
I	0	O	reviews
m	0	O	reviews
a	0	O	reviews
F%#king	0	O	reviews
Assh@%$e	0	O	reviews
!!!	0	O	reviews

There	0	O	newsgroup
is	0	O	newsgroup
a	0	O	newsgroup
link	0	O	newsgroup
to	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
contest	0	O	newsgroup
page	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

Iranian	1	B-LOCderiv	weblogs
officials	0	O	weblogs
are	0	O	weblogs
deeply	0	O	weblogs
concerned	0	O	weblogs
about	0	O	weblogs
the	0	O	weblogs
US	1	B-LOCderiv	weblogs
occupation	0	O	weblogs
of	0	O	weblogs
Shindand	1	B-LOC	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
a	0	O	weblogs
massive	0	O	weblogs
Soviet	1	B-ORGpart	weblogs
-	1	I-ORGpart	weblogs
era	1	I-ORGpart	weblogs
airbase	0	O	weblogs
just	0	O	weblogs
30	0	O	weblogs
kilometres	0	O	weblogs
from	0	O	weblogs
Iran	1	B-LOC	weblogs
’s	1	I-LOC	weblogs
border	0	O	weblogs
.	0	O	weblogs

Just	0	O	answers
recently	0	O	answers
discovered	0	O	answers
them	0	O	answers
last	0	O	answers
time	0	O	answers
I	0	O	answers
was	0	O	answers
down	0	O	answers
there	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
they	0	O	answers
're	0	O	answers
very	0	O	answers
nice	0	O	answers
)	0	O	answers
www.kaffeeeis.co.nz	1	B-MISC	answers

However	0	O	answers
if	0	O	answers
you	0	O	answers
plan	0	O	answers
on	0	O	answers
getting	0	O	answers
one	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
then	0	O	answers
get	0	O	answers
more	0	O	answers
than	0	O	answers
one	0	O	answers
at	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
same	0	O	answers
time	0	O	answers
they	0	O	answers
need	0	O	answers
company	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

Follow	0	O	newsgroup
Katrina	1	B-MISC	newsgroup
's	1	I-MISC	newsgroup
path	0	O	newsgroup

If	0	O	newsgroup
sites	0	O	newsgroup
next	0	O	newsgroup
to	0	O	newsgroup
you	0	O	newsgroup
do	0	O	newsgroup
n't	0	O	newsgroup
have	0	O	newsgroup
what	0	O	newsgroup
you	0	O	newsgroup
want	0	O	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
contact	0	O	newsgroup
your	0	O	newsgroup
nearest	0	O	newsgroup
comp.sources.unix	1	B-MISC	newsgroup
archive	0	O	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
or	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
moderator	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

Moving	0	O	reviews
out	0	O	reviews
as	0	O	reviews
soon	0	O	reviews
as	0	O	reviews
our	0	O	reviews
lease	0	O	reviews
is	0	O	reviews
up	0	O	reviews
.	0	O	reviews

Especially	0	O	reviews
high	0	O	reviews
end	0	O	reviews
keep	0	O	reviews
sake	0	O	reviews
sort	0	O	reviews
of	0	O	reviews
clothing	0	O	reviews
that	0	O	reviews
you	0	O	reviews
just	0	O	reviews
ca	0	O	reviews
nt	0	O	reviews
find	0	O	reviews
in	0	O	reviews
a	0	O	reviews
lot	0	O	reviews
of	0	O	reviews
stores	0	O	reviews
.	0	O	reviews

Stay	0	O	reviews
away	0	O	reviews
from	0	O	reviews
this	0	O	reviews
dealership	0	O	reviews
!!!	0	O	reviews

The	0	O	email
rate	0	O	email
schedule	0	O	email
on	0	O	email
Tennessee	1	B-LOC	email
should	0	O	email
be	0	O	email
either	0	O	email
NET	0	O	email
-	0	O	email
2	0	O	email
or	0	O	email
NET	0	O	email
-	0	O	email
284	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

As	0	O	answers
you	0	O	answers
're	0	O	answers
from	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
States	1	B-LOC	answers
you	0	O	answers
'll	0	O	answers
have	0	O	answers
much	0	O	answers
more	0	O	answers
fun	0	O	answers
in	0	O	answers
London	1	B-LOC	answers
.	0	O	answers

No	0	O	reviews
wine	0	O	reviews
glasses	0	O	reviews
.	0	O	reviews

And	0	O	answers
then	0	O	answers
there	0	O	answers
’s	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
rain	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

If	0	O	answers
you	0	O	answers
would	0	O	answers
like	0	O	answers
more	0	O	answers
on	0	O	answers
sexing	0	O	answers
out	0	O	answers
Aplocheilus	0	O	answers
lineatus	0	O	answers
take	0	O	answers
a	0	O	answers
look	0	O	answers
at	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
discussion	0	O	answers
in	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
first	0	O	answers
source	0	O	answers
below	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

Soldiers	0	O	newsgroup
with	0	O	newsgroup
vital	0	O	newsgroup
training	0	O	newsgroup
and	0	O	newsgroup
know	0	O	newsgroup
-	0	O	newsgroup
how	0	O	newsgroup
are	0	O	newsgroup
refusing	0	O	newsgroup
to	0	O	newsgroup
re-enlist	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

Is	0	O	email
there	0	O	email
anyone	0	O	email
else	0	O	email
in	0	O	email
EGM	1	B-ORG	email
that	0	O	email
could	0	O	email
participate	0	O	email
?	0	O	email

28	0	O	newsgroup
-	0	O	newsgroup
Number	0	O	newsgroup
of	0	O	newsgroup
vacation	0	O	newsgroup
days	0	O	newsgroup
Bush	1	B-PER	newsgroup
took	0	O	newsgroup
in	0	O	newsgroup
August	0	O	newsgroup
2003	0	O	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
second	0	O	newsgroup
-	0	O	newsgroup
longest	0	O	newsgroup
vacation	0	O	newsgroup
of	0	O	newsgroup
any	0	O	newsgroup
president	0	O	newsgroup
in	0	O	newsgroup
US	1	B-LOCderiv	newsgroup
history	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

I	0	O	email
'm	0	O	email
handling	0	O	email
the	0	O	email
afternoon	0	O	email
--	0	O	email
I	0	O	email
think	0	O	email
that	0	O	email
Harry	1	B-PER	email
has	0	O	email
this	0	O	email
morning	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

Please	0	O	email
respond	0	O	email
to	0	O	email
Mary.Ellenberger@enron.com	1	B-PER	email

Current	0	O	email
Salary	0	O	email
:	0	O	email
$	1	B-MISC	email
47,500	0	O	email

True	0	O	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
there	0	O	newsgroup
are	0	O	newsgroup
about	0	O	newsgroup
300,000	0	O	newsgroup
wolves	0	O	newsgroup
and	0	O	newsgroup
wolf	0	O	newsgroup
hybrids	0	O	newsgroup
kept	0	O	newsgroup
as	0	O	newsgroup
pets	0	O	newsgroup
in	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
United	1	B-LOC	newsgroup
States	1	I-LOC	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

Nancy	1	B-PER	email

Depends	0	O	answers
on	0	O	answers
what	0	O	answers
you	0	O	answers
want	0	O	answers
in	0	O	answers
a	0	O	answers
pet	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
be	0	O	answers
honest	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

Westfield	1	B-ORG	reviews
and	0	O	reviews
Rt	1	B-ORG	reviews
1	1	I-ORG	reviews
do	0	O	reviews
it	0	O	reviews
well	0	O	reviews
,	0	O	reviews
WHY	0	O	reviews
CA	0	O	reviews
NT	0	O	reviews
U	0	O	reviews
????	0	O	reviews

WWW	0	O	reviews
-	0	O	reviews
Wonderful	0	O	reviews
Wild	0	O	reviews
Wildernest	1	B-ORG	reviews
inn	1	I-ORG	reviews

Unless	0	O	answers
you	0	O	answers
plan	0	O	answers
on	0	O	answers
being	0	O	answers
late	0	O	answers
for	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
bridal	0	O	answers
shower	0	O	answers
you	0	O	answers
might	0	O	answers
want	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
post	0	O	answers
this	0	O	answers
again	0	O	answers
in	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
L.A.	1	B-LOC	answers
section	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

Yes	0	O	email
maam	0	O	email
,	0	O	email
she	0	O	email
's	0	O	email
UBS	1	B-ORG	email
now	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

As	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
year	0	O	newsgroup
progresses	0	O	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
more	0	O	newsgroup
impressive	0	O	newsgroup
your	0	O	newsgroup
ideas	0	O	newsgroup
and	0	O	newsgroup
works	0	O	newsgroup
become	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

500	0	O	newsgroup
-	0	O	newsgroup
Number	0	O	newsgroup
of	0	O	newsgroup
days	0	O	newsgroup
Bush	1	B-PER	newsgroup
has	0	O	newsgroup
spent	0	O	newsgroup
all	0	O	newsgroup
or	0	O	newsgroup
part	0	O	newsgroup
of	0	O	newsgroup
his	0	O	newsgroup
time	0	O	newsgroup
away	0	O	newsgroup
from	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
White	1	B-LOC	newsgroup
House	1	I-LOC	newsgroup
at	0	O	newsgroup
his	0	O	newsgroup
ranch	0	O	newsgroup
in	0	O	newsgroup
Crawford	1	B-LOC	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
Texas	1	B-LOC	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
his	0	O	newsgroup
parents	0	O	newsgroup
'	0	O	newsgroup
retreat	0	O	newsgroup
in	0	O	newsgroup
Kennebunkport	1	B-LOC	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
Maine	1	B-LOC	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
or	0	O	newsgroup
Camp	1	B-LOC	newsgroup
David	1	I-LOC	newsgroup
as	0	O	newsgroup
of	0	O	newsgroup
1	0	O	newsgroup
April	0	O	newsgroup
2004	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

83	0	O	newsgroup
-	0	O	newsgroup
Number	0	O	newsgroup
of	0	O	newsgroup
times	0	O	newsgroup
Bush	1	B-PER	newsgroup
mentioned	0	O	newsgroup
Saddam	1	B-PER	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
Iraq	1	B-LOC	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
or	0	O	newsgroup
regime	0	O	newsgroup
(	0	O	newsgroup
as	0	O	newsgroup
in	0	O	newsgroup
change	0	O	newsgroup
)	0	O	newsgroup
in	0	O	newsgroup
his	0	O	newsgroup
three	0	O	newsgroup
State	1	B-MISC	newsgroup
of	1	I-MISC	newsgroup
the	1	I-MISC	newsgroup
Union	1	I-MISC	newsgroup
addresses	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

How	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
train	0	O	answers
my	0	O	answers
puppy	0	O	answers
?	0	O	answers

Thane	1	B-PER	email
is	0	O	email
in	0	O	email
Austin	1	B-LOC	email
on	0	O	email
Friday	0	O	email
,	0	O	email
but	0	O	email
is	0	O	email
available	0	O	email
by	0	O	email
phone	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

03/15/2001	0	O	email
04:03	0	O	email
PM	0	O	email

I	0	O	email
know	0	O	email
that	0	O	email
Jeff	1	B-PER	email
is	0	O	email
in	0	O	email
Portland	1	B-LOC	email
.	0	O	email

Yahoo!	1	B-ORG	newsgroup

<<	0	O	email
ld2d-#69366-1.DOC	1	B-MISC	email
>>	0	O	email
<<	0	O	email
ld2d-#69345-1.DOC	1	B-MISC	email
>>	0	O	email
?	0	O	email
<<	0	O	email
ld2d-#69397-1.DOC	1	B-MISC	email
>>	0	O	email
<<	0	O	email
ld2d-#69396-1.DOC	1	B-MISC	email
>>	0	O	email
<<	0	O	email
ld2d-#69377-1.XLS	1	B-MISC	email
>>	0	O	email
<<	0	O	email
ld2d-#69381-1.DOC	1	B-MISC	email
>>	0	O	email
<<	0	O	email
ld2d-#69366-1.DOC	1	B-MISC	email
>>	0	O	email
<<	0	O	email
ld2d-#69336-1.XLS	1	B-MISC	email
>>	0	O	email
<<	0	O	email
Primary	1	B-MISC	email
Rights	1	I-MISC	email
4-12	1	I-MISC	email
.doc	1	I-MISC	email
>>	0	O	email
<<	0	O	email
ld2d-#69334-1.DOC	1	B-MISC	email
>>	0	O	email
<<	0	O	email
ld2d-#69345-1.DOC	1	B-MISC	email
>>	0	O	email

Over	0	O	reviews
priced	0	O	reviews
for	0	O	reviews
students	0	O	reviews
to	0	O	reviews
learn	0	O	reviews
!	0	O	reviews

If	0	O	answers
you	0	O	answers
were	0	O	answers
born	0	O	answers
elsewhere	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
start	0	O	answers
here	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

The	0	O	answers
federal	0	O	answers
sites	0	O	answers
of	0	O	answers
Washington	1	B-LOC	answers
,	0	O	answers
DC	1	B-LOC	answers
.	0	O	answers

11/29/2000	0	O	email
04:31	0	O	email
PM	0	O	email

When	0	O	email
she	0	O	email
was	0	O	email
diagnosed	0	O	email
with	0	O	email
the	0	O	email
flesh	0	O	email
eating	0	O	email
disease	0	O	email
the	0	O	email
doctor	0	O	email
gave	0	O	email
her	0	O	email
13	0	O	email
years	0	O	email
to	0	O	email
live	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

you	0	O	answers
have	0	O	answers
brought	0	O	answers
someone	0	O	answers
else	0	O	answers
into	0	O	answers
his	0	O	answers
territory	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
he	0	O	answers
needs	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
be	0	O	answers
reminded	0	O	answers
that	0	O	answers
you	0	O	answers
still	0	O	answers
love	0	O	answers
him	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
support	0	O	answers
his	0	O	answers
claim	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
his	0	O	answers
space	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

By	0	O	weblogs
the	0	O	weblogs
time	0	O	weblogs
it	0	O	weblogs
was	0	O	weblogs
over	0	O	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
Bush	1	B-PER	weblogs
had	0	O	weblogs
served	0	O	weblogs
nearly	0	O	weblogs
two	0	O	weblogs
years	0	O	weblogs
.	0	O	weblogs

For	0	O	email
banks	0	O	email
incorporated	0	O	email
in	0	O	email
a	0	O	email
non-approved	0	O	email
jurisdiction	0	O	email
,	0	O	email
it	0	O	email
may	0	O	email
be	0	O	email
possible	0	O	email
for	0	O	email
them	0	O	email
to	0	O	email
trade	0	O	email
out	0	O	email
of	0	O	email
a	0	O	email
branch	0	O	email
located	0	O	email
in	0	O	email
an	0	O	email
approved	0	O	email
jurisdiction	0	O	email
(	0	O	email
i.e.	0	O	email
U.S.	1	B-LOCderiv	email
and	0	O	email
U.K.	1	B-LOCderiv	email
branches	0	O	email
)	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

What	0	O	newsgroup
manner	0	O	newsgroup
of	0	O	newsgroup
maniac	0	O	newsgroup
would	0	O	newsgroup
undertake	0	O	newsgroup
such	0	O	newsgroup
a	0	O	newsgroup
dangerous	0	O	newsgroup
course	0	O	newsgroup
?	0	O	newsgroup

The	0	O	reviews
white	0	O	reviews
pages	0	O	reviews
allowed	0	O	reviews
me	0	O	reviews
to	0	O	reviews
get	0	O	reviews
in	0	O	reviews
touch	0	O	reviews
with	0	O	reviews
parents	0	O	reviews
of	0	O	reviews
my	0	O	reviews
high	0	O	reviews
school	0	O	reviews
friends	0	O	reviews
so	0	O	reviews
that	0	O	reviews
I	0	O	reviews
could	0	O	reviews
track	0	O	reviews
people	0	O	reviews
down	0	O	reviews
one	0	O	reviews
by	0	O	reviews
one	0	O	reviews
and	0	O	reviews
the	0	O	reviews
restaurant	0	O	reviews
section	0	O	reviews
is	0	O	reviews
basically	0	O	reviews
my	0	O	reviews
cookbook	0	O	reviews
.	0	O	reviews

Budgies	0	O	answers
are	0	O	answers
breast	0	O	answers
feeding	0	O	answers
birds	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
it	0	O	answers
may	0	O	answers
be	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
male	0	O	answers
is	0	O	answers
bisexual	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

Climb	0	O	answers
Mount	1	B-LOC	answers
Fuji	1	I-LOC	answers
.	0	O	answers

An	0	O	newsgroup
examination	0	O	newsgroup
of	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
ramifications	0	O	newsgroup
of	0	O	newsgroup
such	0	O	newsgroup
an	0	O	newsgroup
attack	0	O	newsgroup
is	0	O	newsgroup
desperately	0	O	newsgroup
in	0	O	newsgroup
order	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

How	0	O	reviews
do	0	O	reviews
you	0	O	reviews
lose	0	O	reviews
a	0	O	reviews
drawer	0	O	reviews
.	0	O	reviews

$	1	B-MISC	newsgroup
113	0	O	newsgroup
m	0	O	newsgroup
-	0	O	newsgroup
Amount	0	O	newsgroup
raised	0	O	newsgroup
by	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
Bush	1	B-PERpart	newsgroup
-	1	I-PERpart	newsgroup
Cheney	1	I-PERpart	newsgroup
2000	0	O	newsgroup
campaign	0	O	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
most	0	O	newsgroup
in	0	O	newsgroup
American	1	B-LOCderiv	newsgroup
electoral	0	O	newsgroup
history	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

In	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
world	0	O	newsgroup
press	0	O	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
commentators	0	O	newsgroup
predict	0	O	newsgroup
that	0	O	newsgroup
Katrina	1	B-MISC	newsgroup
will	0	O	newsgroup
make	0	O	newsgroup
a	0	O	newsgroup
profound	0	O	newsgroup
change	0	O	newsgroup
in	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
way	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
US	1	B-ORG	newsgroup
is	0	O	newsgroup
perceived	0	O	newsgroup
at	0	O	newsgroup
home	0	O	newsgroup
and	0	O	newsgroup
abroad	0	O	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
especially	0	O	newsgroup
following	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
scenes	0	O	newsgroup
of	0	O	newsgroup
poverty	0	O	newsgroup
and	0	O	newsgroup
racial	0	O	newsgroup
divisions	0	O	newsgroup
they	0	O	newsgroup
believe	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
disaster	0	O	newsgroup
has	0	O	newsgroup
revealed	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

However	0	O	reviews
,	0	O	reviews
during	0	O	reviews
the	0	O	reviews
test	0	O	reviews
,	0	O	reviews
they	0	O	reviews
did	0	O	reviews
whatever	0	O	reviews
they	0	O	reviews
can	0	O	reviews
to	0	O	reviews
get	0	O	reviews
my	0	O	reviews
test	0	O	reviews
failed	0	O	reviews
.	0	O	reviews

‘’	0	O	weblogs
We	0	O	weblogs
have	0	O	weblogs
a	0	O	weblogs
very	0	O	weblogs
small	0	O	weblogs
number	0	O	weblogs
of	0	O	weblogs
forces	0	O	weblogs
in	0	O	weblogs
Shindand	1	B-LOC	weblogs
with	0	O	weblogs
a	0	O	weblogs
few	0	O	weblogs
helicopters	0	O	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
’’	0	O	weblogs
says	0	O	weblogs
Barno	1	B-PER	weblogs
.	0	O	weblogs

Iris	1	B-PER	email
,	0	O	email

The	0	O	reviews
BEST	0	O	reviews

That	0	O	newsgroup
was	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
day	0	O	newsgroup
that	0	O	newsgroup
GOD	0	O	newsgroup
'S	0	O	newsgroup
CURSE	0	O	newsgroup
fell	0	O	newsgroup
upon	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
world	0	O	newsgroup
of	0	O	newsgroup
Rock	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

give	0	O	answers
them	0	O	answers
time	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
set	0	O	answers
up	0	O	answers
their	0	O	answers
territories	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
once	0	O	answers
you	0	O	answers
bring	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
new	0	O	answers
kitten	0	O	answers
out	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
pay	0	O	answers
a	0	O	answers
lot	0	O	answers
of	0	O	answers
attention	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
male	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

Like	0	O	newsgroup
it	0	O	newsgroup
or	0	O	newsgroup
not	0	O	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
for	0	O	newsgroup
good	0	O	newsgroup
or	0	O	newsgroup
bad	0	O	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
we	0	O	newsgroup
are	0	O	newsgroup
here	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

They	0	O	answers
will	0	O	answers
whistle	0	O	answers
when	0	O	answers
they	0	O	answers
hear	0	O	answers
you	0	O	answers
as	0	O	answers
an	0	O	answers
encouragement	0	O	answers
for	0	O	answers
you	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
give	0	O	answers
them	0	O	answers
a	0	O	answers
treat	0	O	answers
like	0	O	answers
leaf	0	O	answers
lettuce	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

Asked	0	O	reviews
for	0	O	reviews
bar	0	O	reviews
-	0	O	reviews
b	0	O	reviews
-	0	O	reviews
que	0	O	reviews
sauce	0	O	reviews
never	0	O	reviews
got	0	O	reviews
it	0	O	reviews
.	0	O	reviews

looks	0	O	email
fine	0	O	email

Gates	0	O	reviews
worked	0	O	reviews
30	0	O	reviews
%	0	O	reviews
of	0	O	reviews
the	0	O	reviews
time	0	O	reviews
at	0	O	reviews
best	0	O	reviews
.	0	O	reviews

(	0	O	answers
Because	0	O	answers
apparently	0	O	answers
my	0	O	answers
mom	0	O	answers
is	0	O	answers
very	0	O	answers
picky	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
she	0	O	answers
says	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
bird	0	O	answers
might	0	O	answers
get	0	O	answers
sick	0	O	answers
if	0	O	answers
it	0	O	answers
does	0	O	answers
n't	0	O	answers
eat	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
right	0	O	answers
food	0	O	answers
)	0	O	answers
IS	0	O	answers
there	0	O	answers
any	0	O	answers
specific	0	O	answers
food	0	O	answers
I	0	O	answers
might	0	O	answers
find	0	O	answers
at	0	O	answers
any	0	O	answers
pet	0	O	answers
shop	0	O	answers
?	0	O	answers

Bill	1	B-PER	email

STEP	0	O	newsgroup
FOUR	0	O	newsgroup
:	0	O	newsgroup

WHAT	0	O	email
:	0	O	email
Happy	0	O	email
Hour	0	O	email
for	0	O	email
John	1	B-PER	email
Suarez	1	I-PER	email

The	0	O	answers
American	1	B-LOCderiv	answers
people	0	O	answers
were	0	O	answers
NOT	0	O	answers
having	0	O	answers
any	0	O	answers
of	0	O	answers
it	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
elected	0	O	answers
Richard	1	B-PER	answers
Nixon	1	I-PER	answers
to	0	O	answers
fix	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
mess	0	O	answers
LBJ	1	B-ORG	answers
had	0	O	answers
made	0	O	answers
(	0	O	answers
not	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
surrender	0	O	answers
like	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
antiwar	0	O	answers
movement	0	O	answers
was	0	O	answers
demanding	0	O	answers
)	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

The	0	O	reviews
service	0	O	reviews
was	0	O	reviews
just	0	O	reviews
about	0	O	reviews
as	0	O	reviews
good	0	O	reviews
as	0	O	reviews
I	0	O	reviews
'd	0	O	reviews
get	0	O	reviews
in	0	O	reviews
NYC	1	B-LOC	reviews
(	0	O	reviews
that	0	O	reviews
means	0	O	reviews
it	0	O	reviews
was	0	O	reviews
poor	0	O	reviews
)	0	O	reviews
and	0	O	reviews
the	0	O	reviews
food	0	O	reviews
was	0	O	reviews
almost	0	O	reviews
mediocre	0	O	reviews
.	0	O	reviews

I	0	O	answers
m	0	O	answers
around	0	O	answers
5	0	O	answers
'	0	O	answers
2	0	O	answers
-	0	O	answers
5	0	O	answers
'	0	O	answers
4	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
11	0	O	answers
years	0	O	answers
old	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
i	0	O	answers
m	0	O	answers
wondering	0	O	answers
what	0	O	answers
size	0	O	answers
horse	0	O	answers
i	0	O	answers
'll	0	O	answers
need	0	O	answers
that	0	O	answers
i	0	O	answers
wo	0	O	answers
nt	0	O	answers
grow	0	O	answers
out	0	O	answers
of	0	O	answers
quickly	0	O	answers
?	0	O	answers

Same	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
when	0	O	answers
I	0	O	answers
'm	0	O	answers
galloping	0	O	answers
in	0	O	answers
an	0	O	answers
open	0	O	answers
space	0	O	answers
like	0	O	answers
that	0	O	answers
I	0	O	answers
can	0	O	answers
just	0	O	answers
forget	0	O	answers
everything	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

But	0	O	newsgroup
that	0	O	newsgroup
’s	0	O	newsgroup
not	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
case	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

Even	0	O	reviews
though	0	O	reviews
you	0	O	reviews
are	0	O	reviews
expensive	0	O	reviews
.	0	O	reviews

Did	0	O	answers
your	0	O	answers
vet	0	O	answers
take	0	O	answers
radiographs	0	O	answers
(	0	O	answers
x	0	O	answers
-	0	O	answers
rays	0	O	answers
)	0	O	answers
?	0	O	answers

Vince	1	B-PER	email

When	0	O	newsgroup
not	0	O	newsgroup
in	0	O	newsgroup
Texas	1	B-LOC	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
I	0	O	newsgroup
lived	0	O	newsgroup
in	0	O	newsgroup
LA	1	B-LOC	newsgroup
and	0	O	newsgroup
San	1	B-LOC	newsgroup
Francisco	1	I-LOC	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

Even	0	O	weblogs
for	0	O	weblogs
those	0	O	weblogs
who	0	O	weblogs
later	0	O	weblogs
abstain	0	O	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
"	0	O	weblogs
visual	0	O	weblogs
-	0	O	weblogs
spatial	0	O	weblogs
abilities	0	O	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
abstraction	0	O	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
problem	0	O	weblogs
solving	0	O	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
and	0	O	weblogs
short	0	O	weblogs
-	0	O	weblogs
term	0	O	weblogs
memory	0	O	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
are	0	O	weblogs
the	0	O	weblogs
slowest	0	O	weblogs
to	0	O	weblogs
recover	0	O	weblogs
.	0	O	weblogs
"	0	O	weblogs

Maybe	0	O	newsgroup
one	0	O	newsgroup
day	0	O	newsgroup
they	0	O	newsgroup
will	0	O	newsgroup
allow	0	O	newsgroup
space	0	O	newsgroup
tourism	0	O	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
(	0	O	newsgroup
hopefully	0	O	newsgroup
that	0	O	newsgroup
will	0	O	newsgroup
be	0	O	newsgroup
in	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
near	0	O	newsgroup
future	0	O	newsgroup
)	0	O	newsgroup
although	0	O	newsgroup
I	0	O	newsgroup
would	0	O	newsgroup
recommend	0	O	newsgroup
that	0	O	newsgroup
NASA	1	B-ORG	newsgroup
build	0	O	newsgroup
new	0	O	newsgroup
shuttles	0	O	newsgroup
instead	0	O	newsgroup
of	0	O	newsgroup
trying	0	O	newsgroup
to	0	O	newsgroup
preserve	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
older	0	O	newsgroup
ones	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

The	0	O	email
forum	0	O	email
is	0	O	email
expected	0	O	email
to	0	O	email
be	0	O	email
invited	0	O	email
testimony	0	O	email
only	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

I	0	O	email
am	0	O	email
available	0	O	email
after	0	O	email
Rick	1	B-PER	email
's	1	I-PER	email
Friday	0	O	email
budget	0	O	email
meeting	0	O	email
...	0	O	email
are	0	O	email
you	0	O	email
available	0	O	email
then	0	O	email
?	0	O	email

I	0	O	answers
bet	0	O	answers
you	0	O	answers
also	0	O	answers
did	0	O	answers
take	0	O	answers
charcoal	0	O	answers
as	0	O	answers
it	0	O	answers
is	0	O	answers
used	0	O	answers
for	0	O	answers
barbecue	0	O	answers
which	0	O	answers
does	0	O	answers
not	0	O	answers
get	0	O	answers
as	0	O	answers
hot	0	O	answers
as	0	O	answers
real	0	O	answers
coal	0	O	answers
(	0	O	answers
e.g.	0	O	answers
for	0	O	answers
blacksmithing	0	O	answers
one	0	O	answers
needs	0	O	answers
coal	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
not	0	O	answers
barbecue	0	O	answers
charcoal	0	O	answers
)	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

Jared	1	B-PER	email
,	0	O	email
Ruth	1	B-PER	email
and	0	O	email
I	0	O	email
are	0	O	email
going	0	O	email
to	0	O	email
go	0	O	email
over	0	O	email
all	0	O	email
the	0	O	email
Florida	1	B-LOC	email
activity	0	O	email
tomorrow	0	O	email
morning	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

As	0	O	email
for	0	O	email
Ted	1	B-PER	email
,	0	O	email
things	0	O	email
are	0	O	email
still	0	O	email
going	0	O	email
well	0	O	email
although	0	O	email
I	0	O	email
have	0	O	email
n't	0	O	email
see	0	O	email
him	0	O	email
at	0	O	email
all	0	O	email
this	0	O	email
week	0	O	email
(	0	O	email
we	0	O	email
are	0	O	email
two	0	O	email
very	0	O	email
busy	0	O	email
people	0	O	email
)	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

W.	1	B-PER	email
Don	1	I-PER	email
Germany	1	I-PER	email
,	1	I-PER	email
Jr.	1	I-PER	email
2301	0	O	email
N	0	O	email
Brazosport	1	B-LOC	email
Blvd	1	I-LOC	email
B	0	O	email
3611	0	O	email
,	0	O	email
Investment	0	O	email
Recovery	0	O	email
Freeport	1	B-LOC	email
,	0	O	email
Texas	1	B-LOC	email
77541	0	O	email
Pager	0	O	email
1	0	O	email
800	0	O	email
451	0	O	email
0491	0	O	email
(	0	O	email
0448	0	O	email
)	0	O	email
Office	0	O	email
979	0	O	email
238	0	O	email
2102	0	O	email
Home	0	O	email
979	0	O	email
548	0	O	email
7034	0	O	email

May	0	O	newsgroup
God	0	O	newsgroup
help	0	O	newsgroup
us	0	O	newsgroup
all	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

Chris	1	B-PER	email

----------------------------------------------------------------------	0	O	newsgroup

This	0	O	reviews
place	0	O	reviews
is	0	O	reviews
top	0	O	reviews
notch	0	O	reviews
and	0	O	reviews
highly	0	O	reviews
affordable	0	O	reviews
!	0	O	reviews

-	0	O	answers
Filet	0	O	answers
-	0	O	answers
O	0	O	answers
-	0	O	answers
Fish	0	O	answers

He	0	O	reviews
says	0	O	reviews
:	0	O	reviews
I	0	O	reviews
not	0	O	reviews
know	0	O	reviews
that	0	O	reviews
town	0	O	reviews
,	0	O	reviews
I	0	O	reviews
have	0	O	reviews
to	0	O	reviews
get	0	O	reviews
to	0	O	reviews
work	0	O	reviews
,	0	O	reviews
I	0	O	reviews
'm	0	O	reviews
in	0	O	reviews
PHILLY	1	B-LOC	reviews
.	0	O	reviews

This	0	O	reviews
place	0	O	reviews
rocked	0	O	reviews
.	0	O	reviews

Baffled	0	O	reviews
by	0	O	reviews
the	0	O	reviews
one	0	O	reviews
-	0	O	reviews
star	0	O	reviews
reviews	0	O	reviews

And	0	O	email
do	0	O	email
you	0	O	email
want	0	O	email
to	0	O	email
do	0	O	email
it	0	O	email
on	0	O	email
a	0	O	email
Saturday	0	O	email
or	0	O	email
Sunday	0	O	email
?	0	O	email

I	0	O	email
think	0	O	email
she	0	O	email
just	0	O	email
wants	0	O	email
to	0	O	email
be	0	O	email
able	0	O	email
to	0	O	email
touch	0	O	email
football	0	O	email
players	0	O	email
legs	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

Cures	0	O	newsgroup
kidney	0	O	newsgroup
and	0	O	newsgroup
gall	0	O	newsgroup
bladder	0	O	newsgroup
troubles	0	O	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
gastric	0	O	newsgroup
trouble	0	O	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
dyspepsia	0	O	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
acidity	0	O	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
dysentery	0	O	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
obesity	0	O	newsgroup
and	0	O	newsgroup
liver	0	O	newsgroup
diseases	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

I	0	O	email
'll	0	O	email
be	0	O	email
in	0	O	email
Portland	1	B-LOC	email
but	0	O	email
can	0	O	email
call	0	O	email
you	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

Despite	0	O	weblogs
Sept.	1	B-MISC	weblogs
11	1	I-MISC	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
the	0	O	weblogs
United	1	B-ORG	weblogs
States	1	I-ORG	weblogs
still	0	O	weblogs
supports	0	O	weblogs
the	0	O	weblogs
Kashmir	1	B-LOC	weblogs
groups	0	O	weblogs
that	0	O	weblogs
back	0	O	weblogs
jihad	0	O	weblogs
as	0	O	weblogs
part	0	O	weblogs
of	0	O	weblogs
the	0	O	weblogs
price	0	O	weblogs
Washington	1	B-ORG	weblogs
is	0	O	weblogs
paying	0	O	weblogs
to	0	O	weblogs
keep	0	O	weblogs
Pervez	1	B-PER	weblogs
Musharraf	1	I-PER	weblogs
happy	0	O	weblogs
.	0	O	weblogs

More	0	O	newsgroup
significantly	0	O	newsgroup
,	0	O	newsgroup
China	1	B-ORG	newsgroup
holds	0	O	newsgroup
a	0	O	newsgroup
large	0	O	newsgroup
portion	0	O	newsgroup
of	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
American	1	B-LOCderiv	newsgroup
economy	0	O	newsgroup
in	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
palm	0	O	newsgroup
of	0	O	newsgroup
its	0	O	newsgroup
hand	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

put	0	O	answers
her	0	O	answers
back	0	O	answers
in	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
room	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
keep	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
door	0	O	answers
closed	0	O	answers
for	0	O	answers
a	0	O	answers
week	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

Should	0	O	email
you	0	O	email
have	0	O	email
any	0	O	email
questions	0	O	email
,	0	O	email
feel	0	O	email
free	0	O	email
to	0	O	email
call	0	O	email
me	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

Keep	0	O	email
Your	0	O	email
Powder	0	O	email
Dry	0	O	email
!	0	O	email

Justin	1	B-PER	email

These	0	O	answers
changes	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
while	0	O	answers
significant	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
were	0	O	answers
concentrated	0	O	answers
in	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
elite	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
and	0	O	answers
for	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
vast	0	O	answers
majority	0	O	answers
of	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
population	0	O	answers
life	0	O	answers
was	0	O	answers
little	0	O	answers
changed	0	O	answers
from	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
Middle	1	B-MISC	answers
Ages	1	I-MISC	answers
.	0	O	answers

Let	0	O	email
's	0	O	email
discuss	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

Ordinarily	0	O	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
George	1	B-PER	weblogs
would	0	O	weblogs
come	0	O	weblogs
in	0	O	weblogs
around	0	O	weblogs
noon	0	O	weblogs
;	0	O	weblogs
he	0	O	weblogs
would	0	O	weblogs
ordinarily	0	O	weblogs
leave	0	O	weblogs
around	0	O	weblogs
5:30	0	O	weblogs
or	0	O	weblogs
6:00	0	O	weblogs
in	0	O	weblogs
the	0	O	weblogs
evening	0	O	weblogs
.	0	O	weblogs

Asked	0	O	newsgroup
by	0	O	newsgroup
:	0	O	newsgroup
yheggy	1	B-PER	newsgroup
-	0	O	newsgroup
ga	0	O	newsgroup

My	0	O	reviews
pup	0	O	reviews
has	0	O	reviews
a	0	O	reviews
wonderful	0	O	reviews
temperment	0	O	reviews
and	0	O	reviews
has	0	O	reviews
been	0	O	reviews
a	0	O	reviews
wonderful	0	O	reviews
addition	0	O	reviews
to	0	O	reviews
my	0	O	reviews
family	0	O	reviews
!	0	O	reviews

I	0	O	reviews
would	0	O	reviews
recommend	0	O	reviews
them	0	O	reviews
to	0	O	reviews
anyone	0	O	reviews
!	0	O	reviews

Electricity	1	B-MISC	email
Market	1	I-MISC	email
Design	1	I-MISC	email
Conference	1	I-MISC	email
March	0	O	email
25	0	O	email
-	0	O	email
26	0	O	email
,	0	O	email
2002	0	O	email
,	0	O	email
Atlanta	1	B-LOC	email
,	0	O	email
Georgia	1	B-LOC	email

We	0	O	weblogs
all	0	O	weblogs
know	0	O	weblogs
by	0	O	weblogs
now	0	O	weblogs
that	0	O	weblogs
Bush	1	B-PER	weblogs
did	0	O	weblogs
not	0	O	weblogs
even	0	O	weblogs
do	0	O	weblogs
his	0	O	weblogs
full	0	O	weblogs
service	0	O	weblogs
with	0	O	weblogs
the	0	O	weblogs
Texas	1	B-ORG	weblogs
Air	1	I-ORG	weblogs
National	1	I-ORG	weblogs
Guard	1	I-ORG	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
absenting	0	O	weblogs
himself	0	O	weblogs
to	0	O	weblogs
work	0	O	weblogs
on	0	O	weblogs
the	0	O	weblogs
Alabama	1	B-LOC	weblogs
senate	0	O	weblogs
campaign	0	O	weblogs
of	0	O	weblogs
Winton	1	B-PER	weblogs
"	1	I-PER	weblogs
Red	1	I-PER	weblogs
"	1	I-PER	weblogs
Blount	1	I-PER	weblogs
.	0	O	weblogs

"	0	O	weblogs
All	1	B-MISC	weblogs
Things	1	I-MISC	weblogs
Considered	1	I-MISC	weblogs
(	0	O	weblogs
8:00	0	O	weblogs
PM	0	O	weblogs
ET	0	O	weblogs
)	0	O	weblogs
-	0	O	weblogs
NPR	1	B-ORG	weblogs
March	0	O	weblogs
30	0	O	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
2004	0	O	weblogs
Tuesday	0	O	weblogs

The	0	O	reviews
owners	0	O	reviews
of	0	O	reviews
Bowtie	1	B-ORG	reviews
manged	0	O	reviews
to	0	O	reviews
add	0	O	reviews
something	0	O	reviews
new	0	O	reviews
while	0	O	reviews
preserving	0	O	reviews
what	0	O	reviews
was	0	O	reviews
already	0	O	reviews
there	0	O	reviews
.	0	O	reviews

Hi	0	O	email
Marie	1	B-PER	email

Ben	1	B-PER	email

Seizures	0	O	answers
will	0	O	answers
occur	0	O	answers
when	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
toxins	0	O	answers
that	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
kidney	0	O	answers
normally	0	O	answers
filters	0	O	answers
out	0	O	answers
are	0	O	answers
released	0	O	answers
into	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
blood	0	O	answers
stream	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

If	0	O	email
the	0	O	email
latter	0	O	email
is	0	O	email
the	0	O	email
case	0	O	email
,	0	O	email
we	0	O	email
could	0	O	email
place	0	O	email
both	0	O	email
Sara	1	B-PER	email
and	0	O	email
Elena	1	B-PER	email
in	0	O	email
a	0	O	email
specialist	0	O	email
job	0	O	email
group	0	O	email
(	0	O	email
the	0	O	email
salary	0	O	email
range	0	O	email
is	0	O	email
33	0	O	email
-	0	O	email
66	0	O	email
K	0	O	email
)	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

I	0	O	email
have	0	O	email
inserted	0	O	email
the	0	O	email
company	0	O	email
details	0	O	email
of	0	O	email
Uecomm	1	B-ORG	email
as	0	O	email
requested	0	O	email
.	0	O	email

Thanks	0	O	email

When	0	O	reviews
I	0	O	reviews
inquired	0	O	reviews
he	0	O	reviews
rudely	0	O	reviews
replied	0	O	reviews
"	0	O	reviews
in	0	O	reviews
the	0	O	reviews
morning	0	O	reviews
when	0	O	reviews
things	0	O	reviews
are	0	O	reviews
checked	0	O	reviews
out	0	O	reviews
you	0	O	reviews
'll	0	O	reviews
get	0	O	reviews
it	0	O	reviews
back	0	O	reviews
.	0	O	reviews
"	0	O	reviews

Jeff	1	B-PER	email
Garten	1	I-PER	email

Are	0	O	email
you	0	O	email
really	0	O	email
?	0	O	email

At	0	O	answers
the	0	O	answers
moment	0	O	answers
there	0	O	answers
's	0	O	answers
no	0	O	answers
interest	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
but	0	O	answers
that	0	O	answers
'll	0	O	answers
probably	0	O	answers
change	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

GOODWYN	1	B-PER	weblogs
:	0	O	weblogs
According	0	O	weblogs
to	0	O	weblogs
Archibald	1	B-PER	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
Mr.	0	O	weblogs
Bush	1	B-PER	weblogs
would	0	O	weblogs
also	0	O	weblogs
sometimes	0	O	weblogs
tell	0	O	weblogs
stories	0	O	weblogs
about	0	O	weblogs
his	0	O	weblogs
days	0	O	weblogs
at	0	O	weblogs
Yale	1	B-ORG	weblogs
in	0	O	weblogs
New	1	B-LOC	weblogs
Haven	1	I-LOC	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
and	0	O	weblogs
how	0	O	weblogs
whenever	0	O	weblogs
he	0	O	weblogs
got	0	O	weblogs
pulled	0	O	weblogs
over	0	O	weblogs
for	0	O	weblogs
erratic	0	O	weblogs
driving	0	O	weblogs
,	0	O	weblogs
he	0	O	weblogs
was	0	O	weblogs
let	0	O	weblogs
go	0	O	weblogs
after	0	O	weblogs
the	0	O	weblogs
officers	0	O	weblogs
discovered	0	O	weblogs
he	0	O	weblogs
was	0	O	weblogs
the	0	O	weblogs
grandson	0	O	weblogs
of	0	O	weblogs
a	0	O	weblogs
Connecticut	1	B-LOC	weblogs
US	1	B-LOCderiv	weblogs
senator	0	O	weblogs
.	0	O	weblogs

$	1	B-MISC	newsgroup
6.1	0	O	newsgroup
m	0	O	newsgroup
-	0	O	newsgroup
Amount	0	O	newsgroup
the	0	O	newsgroup
EPA	1	B-ORG	newsgroup
historically	0	O	newsgroup
valued	0	O	newsgroup
each	0	O	newsgroup
human	0	O	newsgroup
life	0	O	newsgroup
when	0	O	newsgroup
conducting	0	O	newsgroup
economic	0	O	newsgroup
analyses	0	O	newsgroup
of	0	O	newsgroup
proposed	0	O	newsgroup
regulations	0	O	newsgroup
.	0	O	newsgroup

Sara	1	B-PER	email

I	0	O	answers
will	0	O	answers
also	0	O	answers
be	0	O	answers
having	0	O	answers
my	0	O	answers
other	0	O	answers
vet	0	O	answers
up	0	O	answers
who	0	O	answers
's	0	O	answers
a	0	O	answers
chiro	0	O	answers
&	0	O	answers
acupuncturist	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
evaluate	0	O	answers
him	0	O	answers
for	0	O	answers
wobblers	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

Kay	1	B-PER	email
Mann	1	I-PER	email

You	0	O	answers
do	0	O	answers
n't	0	O	answers
say	0	O	answers
what	0	O	answers
color	0	O	answers
Silkie	0	O	answers
or	0	O	answers
Sussex	1	B-LOCderiv	answers
you	0	O	answers
are	0	O	answers
dealing	0	O	answers
with	0	O	answers
so	0	O	answers
I	0	O	answers
ca	0	O	answers
n't	0	O	answers
say	0	O	answers
what	0	O	answers
color	0	O	answers
your	0	O	answers
chicks	0	O	answers
would	0	O	answers
be	0	O	answers
likely	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
be	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers

The	0	O	answers
difference	0	O	answers
is	0	O	answers
what	0	O	answers
they	0	O	answers
need	0	O	answers
to	0	O	answers
live	0	O	answers
,	0	O	answers
VS	0	O	answers
what	0	O	answers
's	0	O	answers
ideal	0	O	answers
for	0	O	answers
them	0	O	answers
.	0	O	answers
